[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Treasure Hunt,\" the title of quest giver Isaias is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Treasure Hunt,\" the title of quest giver Isaias is Explorer King.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Treasure Hunt,\" the title of quest giver Isaias is Treasure King.",
    "correctAnswer": "Explorer King",
    "wrongAnswer": "Treasure King"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Treasure Hunt,\" the Treasure Chest is hidden inside ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Treasure Hunt,\" the Treasure Chest is hidden inside a Beetle.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Treasure Hunt,\" the Treasure Chest is hidden inside a Lucky Crystal.",
    "correctAnswer": "a Beetle",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Lucky Crystal"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Bucket List,\" the magic Edward excels at is called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Bucket List,\" the magic Edward excels at is called Thunder Piercer.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Bucket List,\" the magic Edward excels at is called Lightning Piercer.",
    "correctAnswer": "Thunder Piercer",
    "wrongAnswer": "Lightning Piercer"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Bucket List,\" the buff you gain near the Altar increases your ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Bucket List,\" the buff you gain near the Altar increases your DMG.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Bucket List,\" the buff you gain near the Altar increases your Loot Drop Rate.",
    "correctAnswer": "DMG",
    "wrongAnswer": "Loot Drop Rate"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon's Heart,\" the quest giver's name is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon's Heart,\" the quest giver's name is Annie.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon's Heart,\" the quest giver's name is Anna.",
    "correctAnswer": "Annie",
    "wrongAnswer": "Anna"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon's Heart,\" John needs money because his ______ is ill.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon's Heart,\" John needs money because his wife is ill.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon's Heart,\" John needs money because his daughter is ill.",
    "correctAnswer": "wife",
    "wrongAnswer": "daughter"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "questionTemplate": "In the \"Trial of Name\" in the Fame Quest \"Kargula's Tests,\" the Rabbit you need to defeat is called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the \"Trial of Name\" in the Fame Quest \"Kargula's Tests,\" the Rabbit you need to defeat is called Kargula Phantom.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the \"Trial of Name\" in the Fame Quest \"Kargula's Tests,\" the Rabbit you need to defeat is called Kargula Incarnation.",
    "correctAnswer": "Kargula Phantom",
    "wrongAnswer": "Kargula Incarnation"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Kargula's Tests,\" the Chief of Kargula Village is called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Kargula's Tests,\" the Chief of Kargula Village is called Milton.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Kargula's Tests,\" the Chief of Kargula Village is called Hilton.",
    "correctAnswer": "Milton",
    "wrongAnswer": "Hilton"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Reopen the Mine Pit,\" you need to find ______ miners for Max.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Reopen the Mine Pit,\" you need to find 4 miners for Max.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Reopen the Mine Pit,\" you need to find 3 miners for Max.",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "wrongAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Reopen the Mine Pit,\" ______ is disguised as Crystal Ore.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Reopen the Mine Pit,\" Clermont is disguised as Crystal Ore.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Reopen the Mine Pit,\" Abel is disguised as Crystal Ore.",
    "correctAnswer": "Clermont",
    "wrongAnswer": "Abel"
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Talented Tanuki,\" the Lightning Gang Chief is named ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Talented Tanuki,\" the Lightning Gang Chief is named Paco.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Talented Tanuki,\" the Lightning Gang Chief is named Hogan.",
    "correctAnswer": "Paco",
    "wrongAnswer": "Hogan"
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Talented Tanuki\", Hogan is a member of the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Talented Tanuki\", Hogan is a member of the Ham League.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Talented Tanuki\", Hogan is a member of the Lightning Gang.",
    "correctAnswer": "Ham League",
    "wrongAnswer": "Lightning Gang"
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Pirates' Booty,\" Giant Jordan's weapon is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Pirates' Booty,\" Giant Jordan's weapon is an Axe.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Pirates' Booty,\" Giant Jordan's weapon is a Broadsword.",
    "correctAnswer": "an Axe",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Broadsword"
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Abandoned Robots,\" the quest giver Billy is a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Abandoned Robots,\" the quest giver Billy is a feisty little boy.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Abandoned Robots,\" the quest giver Billy is a feisty old man.",
    "correctAnswer": "feisty little boy",
    "wrongAnswer": "feisty old man"
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Abandoned Robots,\" Blockhead is ultimately ______ to leave with Billy.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Abandoned Robots,\" Blockhead is ultimately willing to leave with Billy.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Abandoned Robots,\" Blockhead is ultimately not willing to leave with Billy.",
    "correctAnswer": "willing",
    "wrongAnswer": "not willing"
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Smelly Arachnid,\" the quest giver's name is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Smelly Arachnid,\" the quest giver's name is First Village Chief.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Smelly Arachnid,\" the quest giver's name is Third Village Chief.",
    "correctAnswer": "First Village Chief",
    "wrongAnswer": "Third Village Chief"
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Smelly Arachnid,\" the spider you fight at the end is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Smelly Arachnid,\" the spider you fight at the end is female.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Smelly Arachnid,\" the spider you fight at the end is male.",
    "correctAnswer": "female",
    "wrongAnswer": "male"
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Spritely Blessings,\" the priest guarding the altar is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Spritely Blessings,\" the priest guarding the altar is female.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Spritely Blessings,\" the priest guarding the altar is male.",
    "correctAnswer": "female",
    "wrongAnswer": "male"
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Spritely Blessings,\" the Sprite's Pet is named ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Spritely Blessings,\" the Sprite's Pet is named Little Purple Fuzzball.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Spritely Blessings,\" the Sprite's Pet is named Little Purple Basketball.",
    "correctAnswer": "Little Purple Fuzzball",
    "wrongAnswer": "Little Purple Basketball"
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Keep It Under Wraps,\" the password is \"______ \"",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Keep It Under Wraps,\" the password is \"Dwarves have short legs.\"",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Keep It Under Wraps,\" the password is \"Weaklings have wimpy legs.\"",
    "correctAnswer": "Dwarves have short legs",
    "wrongAnswer": "Weaklings have wimpy legs"
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Keep It Under Wraps,\" Bombino ______ damaged by his own bombs.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Keep It Under Wraps,\" Bombino is damaged by his own bombs.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Keep It Under Wraps,\" Bombino is not damaged by his own bombs.",
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "wrongAnswer": "is not"
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Flame War,\" Miriya destroys the eggs with ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Flame War,\" Miriya destroys the eggs with fire.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Flame War,\" Miriya destroys the eggs with poison.",
    "correctAnswer": "fire",
    "wrongAnswer": "poison"
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Flame War,\" Village Chief Miriya is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Flame War,\" Village Chief Miriya is an old woman.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Flame War,\" Village Chief Miriya is a young woman.",
    "correctAnswer": "an old woman",
    "wrongAnswer": "a young woman"
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Zinnia in Trouble,\" the failed ritual summons ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Zinnia in Trouble,\" the failed ritual summons Fallen Sprites.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Zinnia in Trouble,\" the failed ritual summons Ancient Rexes.",
    "correctAnswer": "Fallen Sprites",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ancient Rexes"
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Zinnia in Trouble,\" the name of the village is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Zinnia in Trouble,\" the name of the village is Floras.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Zinnia in Trouble,\" the name of the village is Leavas.",
    "correctAnswer": "Floras",
    "wrongAnswer": "Leavas"
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Rescue the Sprite,\" the younger sister is named ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Rescue the Sprite,\" the younger sister is named Lola.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Rescue the Sprite,\" the younger sister is named Loli.",
    "correctAnswer": "Lola",
    "wrongAnswer": "Loli"
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Brawner Park,\" the quest giver's name is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Brawner Park,\" the quest giver's name is Doctor Crow.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Brawner Park,\" the quest giver's name is Doctor Crew.",
    "correctAnswer": "Doctor Crow",
    "wrongAnswer": "Doctor Crew"
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Brawner Park,\" Principal Hamon summons a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Brawner Park,\" Principal Hamon summons a Giant Mountain Dragon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Brawner Park,\" Principal Hamon summons a Tiny Mountain Dragon.",
    "correctAnswer": "Giant Mountain Dragon",
    "wrongAnswer": "Tiny Mountain Dragon"
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Delicious Zinnia,\" the Trolls are competing at ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Delicious Zinnia,\" the Trolls are competing at eating.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Delicious Zinnia,\" the Trolls are competing at running.",
    "correctAnswer": "eating",
    "wrongAnswer": "running"
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Delicious Zinnia,\" the Elder uses ______ to attack the Trolls.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Delicious Zinnia,\" the Elder uses Wild Boars to attack the Trolls.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Delicious Zinnia,\" the Elder uses Dinosaurs to attack the Trolls.",
    "correctAnswer": "Wild Boars",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dinosaurs"
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Badlands Demons,\" the quest giver's name is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Badlands Demons,\" the quest giver's name is Watson.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Badlands Demons,\" the quest giver's name is Holmes.",
    "correctAnswer": "Watson",
    "wrongAnswer": "Holmes"
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Badlands Demons,\" the Demons are revealed through ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Badlands Demons,\" the Demons are revealed through Holy Power.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Badlands Demons,\" the Demons are revealed through Exorcism Power.",
    "correctAnswer": "Holy Power",
    "wrongAnswer": "Exorcism Power"
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Prehistoric Giant Bug\", the giant bugs are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Prehistoric Giant Bug\", the giant bugs are Ancient Sickle Spiderlings.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Prehistoric Giant Bug\", the giant bugs are Ancient Bumblebees.",
    "correctAnswer": "Ancient Sickle Spiderlings",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ancient Bumblebees"
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Prehistoric Giant Bug\", the missing Dwarf miner is named ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Prehistoric Giant Bug\", the missing Dwarf miner is named Basil.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Prehistoric Giant Bug\", the missing Dwarf miner is named Jack.",
    "correctAnswer": "Basil",
    "wrongAnswer": "Jack"
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Merchant's Treasure,\" the flowers that eat gold are called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Merchant's Treasure,\" the flowers that eat gold are called Golden Flowertraps.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Merchant's Treasure,\" the flowers that eat gold are called Golden Sunflowers.",
    "correctAnswer": "Golden Flowertraps",
    "wrongAnswer": "Golden Sunflowers"
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Ancient Lord's Sword\", the quest takes place in an ancient ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Ancient Lord's Sword\", the quest takes place in an ancient tomb.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Ancient Lord's Sword\", the quest takes place in an ancient castle.",
    "correctAnswer": "tomb",
    "wrongAnswer": "castle"
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon God's Fury,\" Tyrone asks you to rescue his ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon God's Fury,\" Tyrone asks you to rescue his grandchildren.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon God's Fury,\" Tyrone asks you to rescue his mother.",
    "correctAnswer": "grandchildren",
    "wrongAnswer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon God's Fury,\" of the three siblings, only Reina wants to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon God's Fury,\" of the three siblings, only Reina wants to go home.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Demon God's Fury,\" of the three siblings, only Reina wants to stay.",
    "correctAnswer": "go home",
    "wrongAnswer": "stay"
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Cut to the Core,\" the Keeper of the Ruins is named ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Cut to the Core,\" the Keeper of the Ruins is named Koral.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Cut to the Core,\" the Keeper of the Ruins is named Cori.",
    "correctAnswer": "Koral",
    "wrongAnswer": "Cori"
  },
  {
    "id": "41",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Cut to the Core\", you need to collect ______ Magic Energy Cores in total.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Cut to the Core\", you need to collect 6 Magic Energy Cores in total.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Cut to the Core\", you need to collect 12 Magic Energy Cores in total.",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "wrongAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Penguins Make Bad Pets,\" Gump is lured away from the altar with ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Penguins Make Bad Pets,\" Gump is lured away from the altar with jars.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Penguins Make Bad Pets,\" Gump is lured away from the altar with baseballs.",
    "correctAnswer": "jars",
    "wrongAnswer": "baseballs"
  },
  {
    "id": "43",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Penguins Make Bad Pets\", the Evil Penguins are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Penguins Make Bad Pets\", the Evil Penguins are beating up the villagers.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Penguins Make Bad Pets\", the Evil Penguins are destroying the villagers' houses.",
    "correctAnswer": "beating up the villagers",
    "wrongAnswer": "destroying the villagers' houses"
  },
  {
    "id": "44",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Bandit Battle,\" the father of the two siblings is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Bandit Battle,\" the father of the two siblings is already dead.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Bandit Battle,\" the father of the two siblings is still alive.",
    "correctAnswer": "already dead",
    "wrongAnswer": "still alive"
  },
  {
    "id": "45",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Bandit Battle,\" the kidnapped sibling is named ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Bandit Battle,\" the kidnapped sibling is named Allie.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Bandit Battle,\" the kidnapped sibling is named Al.",
    "correctAnswer": "Allie",
    "wrongAnswer": "Al"
  },
  {
    "id": "46",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Recapture the Castle,\" Benwick Castle is overrun with ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Recapture the Castle,\" Benwick Castle is overrun with Werewolves.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Recapture the Castle,\" Benwick Castle is overrun with Vampires.",
    "correctAnswer": "Werewolves",
    "wrongAnswer": "Vampires"
  },
  {
    "id": "47",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Recapture the Castle,\" Lucy invites you to bathe in ______ spring water shower(s).",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Recapture the Castle,\" Lucy invites you to bathe in 2 spring water shower(s).",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Recapture the Castle,\" Lucy invites you to bathe in 1 spring water shower(s).",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "wrongAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "48",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Iron and Blood,\" the first prisoner to escape is number ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Iron and Blood,\" the first prisoner to escape is number 24601.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Iron and Blood,\" the first prisoner to escape is number 79979.",
    "correctAnswer": "24601",
    "wrongAnswer": "79979"
  },
  {
    "id": "49",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Iron and Blood,\" Joshua is hiding in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Iron and Blood,\" Joshua is hiding in an Equipment Box.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Iron and Blood,\" Joshua is hiding in an Abandoned Robot.",
    "correctAnswer": "an Equipment Box",
    "wrongAnswer": "an Abandoned Robot"
  },
  {
    "id": "50",
    "questionTemplate": "In Oblitus Wood, the area occupied by a group of robots is called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, the area occupied by a group of robots is called Barren Well.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, the area occupied by a group of robots is called Ghostweep Ruins.",
    "correctAnswer": "Barren Well",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ghostweep Ruins"
  },
  {
    "id": "51",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, Andre of Navea asks you to defeat ______ to prove your strength before traveling to Demarech Mines.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, Andre of Navea asks you to defeat an Armored Mine Lion to prove your strength before traveling to Demarech Mines.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, Andre of Navea asks you to defeat a Slimeling to prove your strength before traveling to Demarech Mines.",
    "correctAnswer": "an Armored Mine Lion",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Slimeling"
  },
  {
    "id": "52",
    "questionTemplate": "The demon god worshipped by the Avians of Triatio Highlands is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The demon god worshipped by the Avians of Triatio Highlands is Argus.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The demon god worshipped by the Avians of Triatio Highlands is Shadow Knight.",
    "correctAnswer": "Argus",
    "wrongAnswer": "Shadow Knight"
  },
  {
    "id": "53",
    "questionTemplate": "The object sought by the Shadow Knight in Demarech Mines was the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The object sought by the Shadow Knight in Demarech Mines was the Cube of Gaia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The object sought by the Shadow Knight in Demarech Mines was the Gaia Crystal.",
    "correctAnswer": "Cube of Gaia",
    "wrongAnswer": "Gaia Crystal"
  },
  {
    "id": "54",
    "questionTemplate": "The Beast Statue Altar is a ritual site of the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Beast Statue Altar is a ritual site of the Argus Cult.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Beast Statue Altar is a ritual site of the Stone Hammer Tribe.",
    "correctAnswer": "Argus Cult",
    "wrongAnswer": "Stone Hammer Tribe"
  },
  {
    "id": "55",
    "questionTemplate": "The spirit seen in the forest by the hunter Juno of Triatio Highlands was actually ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The spirit seen in the forest by the hunter Juno of Triatio Highlands was actually an Eidolon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The spirit seen in the forest by the hunter Juno of Triatio Highlands was actually a Human.",
    "correctAnswer": "an Eidolon",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Human"
  },
  {
    "id": "56",
    "questionTemplate": "The Vampire Bats of Fernscall Woods in Candeo Marsh feed on ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Vampire Bats of Fernscall Woods in Candeo Marsh feed on Turtles.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Vampire Bats of Fernscall Woods in Candeo Marsh feed on Unicorns.",
    "correctAnswer": "Turtles",
    "wrongAnswer": "Unicorns"
  },
  {
    "id": "57",
    "questionTemplate": "In the village of Candetonn in Candeo Marsh, the Corpser Bandits' spy is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the village of Candetonn in Candeo Marsh, the Corpser Bandits' spy is Grandpa Will.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the village of Candetonn in Candeo Marsh, the Corpser Bandits' spy is Village Chief Jeffery.",
    "correctAnswer": "Grandpa Will",
    "wrongAnswer": "Village Chief Jeffery"
  },
  {
    "id": "58",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Spirit Separator can be found in the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Spirit Separator can be found in the Starlight Treasure Chest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Spirit Separator can be found in the Moonlight Rabbit's Treasure.",
    "correctAnswer": "Starlight Treasure Chest",
    "wrongAnswer": "Moonlight Rabbit's Treasure"
  },
  {
    "id": "59",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Spirit Separator is stolen by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Spirit Separator is stolen by Maiden Caroline.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Spirit Separator is stolen by Left-Wing Butterfly Maya.",
    "correctAnswer": "Maiden Caroline",
    "wrongAnswer": "Left-Wing Butterfly Maya"
  },
  {
    "id": "60",
    "questionTemplate": "In Candeo Marsh, Mia uses hypnosis on ______ to make them attack the bandits.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Candeo Marsh, Mia uses hypnosis on Vampire Bats to make them attack the bandits.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Candeo Marsh, Mia uses hypnosis on Turtles to make them attack the bandits.",
    "correctAnswer": "Vampire Bats",
    "wrongAnswer": "Turtles"
  },
  {
    "id": "61",
    "questionTemplate": "In the fighting competition in Ventos Prairie, the ______ falls victim to his own trick.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the fighting competition in Ventos Prairie, the Eldest Prince falls victim to his own trick.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the fighting competition in Ventos Prairie, the Second Prince falls victim to his own trick.",
    "correctAnswer": "Eldest Prince",
    "wrongAnswer": "Second Prince"
  },
  {
    "id": "62",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, the key to the Starlight Treasure Chest is hidden in the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the key to the Starlight Treasure Chest is hidden in the Altar of the Moon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the key to the Starlight Treasure Chest is hidden in the Alabastren Temple Ruins.",
    "correctAnswer": "Altar of the Moon",
    "wrongAnswer": "Alabastren Temple Ruins"
  },
  {
    "id": "63",
    "questionTemplate": "The fighting competition at Ventos Prairie takes place in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The fighting competition at Ventos Prairie takes place in Leyline Arena.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The fighting competition at Ventos Prairie takes place in Limelight Arena.",
    "correctAnswer": "Leyline Arena",
    "wrongAnswer": "Limelight Arena"
  },
  {
    "id": "64",
    "questionTemplate": "The research team in Candeo Marsh came to Awlstone Forest to protect ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The research team in Candeo Marsh came to Awlstone Forest to protect Unicorns.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The research team in Candeo Marsh came to Awlstone Forest to protect Turtles.",
    "correctAnswer": "Unicorns",
    "wrongAnswer": "Turtles"
  },
  {
    "id": "65",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, the environmental degradation of Oblitus Wood is caused by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the environmental degradation of Oblitus Wood is caused by Zombies absorbing the earth's energy.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the environmental degradation of Oblitus Wood is caused by Dwarves overusing the earth's resources.",
    "correctAnswer": "Zombies absorbing the earth's energy",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dwarves overusing the earth's resources"
  },
  {
    "id": "66",
    "questionTemplate": "In Oblitus Wood, the Silverflash Tribe attacks the village for occupying the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, the Silverflash Tribe attacks the village for occupying the Krok Pool.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, the Silverflash Tribe attacks the village for occupying the Ore deposits.",
    "correctAnswer": "Krok Pool",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ore deposits"
  },
  {
    "id": "67",
    "questionTemplate": "The Electromagnetic Turret used to fight the robots near Barren Well was brought by ______ to Forest Oblitus.",
    "correctQuestion": "The Electromagnetic Turret used to fight the robots near Barren Well was brought by Analisa to Forest Oblitus.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Electromagnetic Turret used to fight the robots near Barren Well was brought by Augustus to Forest Oblitus.",
    "correctAnswer": "Analisa",
    "wrongAnswer": "Augustus"
  },
  {
    "id": "68",
    "questionTemplate": "In Oblitus Wood, the Varan of Fulcheth Forest are transporting stones to make ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, the Varan of Fulcheth Forest are transporting stones to make an Earth Guard.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, the Varan of Fulcheth Forest are transporting stones to make weapons and armor.",
    "correctAnswer": "an Earth Guard",
    "wrongAnswer": "weapons and armor"
  },
  {
    "id": "69",
    "questionTemplate": "Before the Shadow Knight's appearance, the Sarpa of Candeo Marsh lived only in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Before the Shadow Knight's appearance, the Sarpa of Candeo Marsh lived only in Candeo Core.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Before the Shadow Knight's appearance, the Sarpa of Candeo Marsh lived only in Thousand Water Marsh.",
    "correctAnswer": "Candeo Core",
    "wrongAnswer": "Thousand Water Marsh"
  },
  {
    "id": "70",
    "questionTemplate": "The entrance to Gydaie Glen in Cactakara Forest can be found behind the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The entrance to Gydaie Glen in Cactakara Forest can be found behind the Waterfall.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The entrance to Gydaie Glen in Cactakara Forest can be found behind the East City Ruins.",
    "correctAnswer": "Waterfall",
    "wrongAnswer": "East City Ruins"
  },
  {
    "id": "71",
    "questionTemplate": "The East City Ruins in Cactakara Forest are inhabited by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The East City Ruins in Cactakara Forest are inhabited by Centaurs.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The East City Ruins in Cactakara Forest are inhabited by Sarpa.",
    "correctAnswer": "Centaurs",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sarpa"
  },
  {
    "id": "72",
    "questionTemplate": "The teleporter to East City Ruins was invented by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The teleporter to East City Ruins was invented by Fenrich.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The teleporter to East City Ruins was invented by Akers.",
    "correctAnswer": "Fenrich",
    "wrongAnswer": "Akers"
  },
  {
    "id": "73",
    "questionTemplate": "The inhabitants of Lunarin in Crescent Hill are busy preparing for the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The inhabitants of Lunarin in Crescent Hill are busy preparing for the Crescent Ceremony.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The inhabitants of Lunarin in Crescent Hill are busy preparing for the Flower Field Renovation.",
    "correctAnswer": "Crescent Ceremony",
    "wrongAnswer": "Flower Field Renovation"
  },
  {
    "id": "74",
    "questionTemplate": "The Gnomes of Mistwalker Tribe in Crescent Hill are causing trouble under orders of the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Gnomes of Mistwalker Tribe in Crescent Hill are causing trouble under orders of the Makar.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Gnomes of Mistwalker Tribe in Crescent Hill are causing trouble under orders of the Dwarves.",
    "correctAnswer": "Makar",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dwarves"
  },
  {
    "id": "75",
    "questionTemplate": "The power of Alabastren Temple has been seized by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The power of Alabastren Temple has been seized by Envoy of Gaia Sonjuno.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The power of Alabastren Temple has been seized by Odum Ryan.",
    "correctAnswer": "Envoy of Gaia Sonjuno",
    "wrongAnswer": "Odum Ryan"
  },
  {
    "id": "76",
    "questionTemplate": "When the Shadow Knight was leader of the Templars, he believed the ______ at the top of the Sky Tower could save his wife.",
    "correctQuestion": "When the Shadow Knight was leader of the Templars, he believed the medicine at the top of the Sky Tower could save his wife.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When the Shadow Knight was leader of the Templars, he believed the crystal at the top of the Sky Tower could save his wife.",
    "correctAnswer": "medicine",
    "wrongAnswer": "crystal"
  },
  {
    "id": "77",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, your battle skills are tested at Lunarin Village in Crescent Hill by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, your battle skills are tested at Lunarin Village in Crescent Hill by Foreman Potter.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, your battle skills are tested at Lunarin Village in Crescent Hill by Young Man Halton.",
    "correctAnswer": "Foreman Potter",
    "wrongAnswer": "Young Man Halton"
  },
  {
    "id": "78",
    "questionTemplate": "The Centaurs of East City Ruins are furious because their ______ was stolen.",
    "correctQuestion": "The Centaurs of East City Ruins are furious because their Scroll was stolen.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Centaurs of East City Ruins are furious because their Halo Grass was stolen.",
    "correctAnswer": "Scroll",
    "wrongAnswer": "Halo Grass"
  },
  {
    "id": "79",
    "questionTemplate": "At the beginning of the game, when you wake up in Port Skandia, you are employed as ______",
    "correctQuestion": "At the beginning of the game, when you wake up in Port Skandia, you are employed as a Garrison Member.",
    "wrongQuestion": "At the beginning of the game, when you wake up in Port Skandia, you are employed as an Assistant to the Village Chief.",
    "correctAnswer": "a Garrison Member",
    "wrongAnswer": "an Assistant to the Village Chief"
  },
  {
    "id": "80",
    "questionTemplate": "The location of your first task in Port Skandia is the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The location of your first task in Port Skandia is the Logging Site.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The location of your first task in Port Skandia is the Medical Station.",
    "correctAnswer": "Logging Site",
    "wrongAnswer": "Medical Station"
  },
  {
    "id": "81",
    "questionTemplate": "In Port Skandia, Flower stands near the stone statue in order to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Port Skandia, Flower stands near the stone statue in order to read the letters on it.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Port Skandia, Flower stands near the stone statue in order to clean it.",
    "correctAnswer": "read the letters on it",
    "wrongAnswer": "clean it"
  },
  {
    "id": "82",
    "questionTemplate": "In Port Skandia, Elena's staff is broken and must be recharged with ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Port Skandia, Elena's staff is broken and must be recharged with Gems.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Port Skandia, Elena's staff is broken and must be recharged with Eidolons.",
    "correctAnswer": "Gems",
    "wrongAnswer": "Eidolons"
  },
  {
    "id": "83",
    "questionTemplate": "In Port Skandia, Brian took the Village Chief's ______ to the Hidden Cave.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Port Skandia, Brian took the Village Chief's son to the Hidden Cave.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Port Skandia, Brian took the Village Chief's daughter to the Hidden Cave.",
    "correctAnswer": "son",
    "wrongAnswer": "daughter"
  },
  {
    "id": "84",
    "questionTemplate": "In Demarech Mines, the Shadow Knight brought ______ to help him navigate.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, the Shadow Knight brought Town Mayor Mason to help him navigate.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, the Shadow Knight brought Old Man Harvey to help him navigate.",
    "correctAnswer": "Town Mayor Mason",
    "wrongAnswer": "Old Man Harvey"
  },
  {
    "id": "85",
    "questionTemplate": "You first met Merchant Luther of Demarech Mines at ______",
    "correctQuestion": "You first met Merchant Luther of Demarech Mines at Helonia Coast.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You first met Merchant Luther of Demarech Mines at Crescent Hill.",
    "correctAnswer": "Helonia Coast",
    "wrongAnswer": "Crescent Hill"
  },
  {
    "id": "86",
    "questionTemplate": "At Marauder's Camp, you receive a ______ from Marauder Captain Solomon.",
    "correctQuestion": "At Marauder's Camp, you receive a Miracle Crystal from Marauder Captain Solomon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "At Marauder's Camp, you receive a Cube of Gaia from Marauder Captain Solomon.",
    "correctAnswer": "Miracle Crystal",
    "wrongAnswer": "Cube of Gaia"
  },
  {
    "id": "87",
    "questionTemplate": "Mayor of Helonia Madeline and her daughter Selena lived in ______ before moving to Helonia.",
    "correctQuestion": "Mayor of Helonia Madeline and her daughter Selena lived in Windmill Cottage before moving to Helonia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Mayor of Helonia Madeline and her daughter Selena lived in Watermill Cottage before moving to Helonia.",
    "correctAnswer": "Windmill Cottage",
    "wrongAnswer": "Watermill Cottage"
  },
  {
    "id": "88",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, Braeden uses ______ to fight the pirates in Helonia Coast.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, Braeden uses bombs to fight the pirates in Helonia Coast.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, Braeden uses fishing nets to fight the pirates in Helonia Coast.",
    "correctAnswer": "bombs",
    "wrongAnswer": "fishing nets"
  },
  {
    "id": "89",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, you travelr to Bella's Orchard in Helonia Coast to look for ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, you travelr to Bella's Orchard in Helonia Coast to look for Alchemist Perry.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, you travelr to Bella's Orchard in Helonia Coast to look for Mayor's Daughter Selena.",
    "correctAnswer": "Alchemist Perry",
    "wrongAnswer": "Mayor's Daughter Selena"
  },
  {
    "id": "90",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, the townsfolk of Helonia Coast are being threatened and extorted by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the townsfolk of Helonia Coast are being threatened and extorted by Pirate Adjutant Bluto.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the townsfolk of Helonia Coast are being threatened and extorted by Pirate Leader Mac.",
    "correctAnswer": "Pirate Adjutant Bluto",
    "wrongAnswer": "Pirate Leader Mac"
  },
  {
    "id": "91",
    "questionTemplate": "Deep's Cavern in Triatio Highlands is sealed by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Deep's Cavern in Triatio Highlands is sealed by Left-Wing Butterfly Maya.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Deep's Cavern in Triatio Highlands is sealed by Argus Deacon Zujahla.",
    "correctAnswer": "Left-Wing Butterfly Maya",
    "wrongAnswer": "Argus Deacon Zujahla"
  },
  {
    "id": "92",
    "questionTemplate": "At the Beast Statue Altar in Triatio Highlands, the character in the cage is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "At the Beast Statue Altar in Triatio Highlands, the character in the cage is Puckett.",
    "wrongQuestion": "At the Beast Statue Altar in Triatio Highlands, the character in the cage is Hunter Roger Jones.",
    "correctAnswer": "Puckett",
    "wrongAnswer": "Hunter Roger Jones"
  },
  {
    "id": "93",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Endless Dunes, Akara asks you to search for ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Endless Dunes, Akara asks you to search for a Dragon Egg.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Endless Dunes, Akara asks you to search for the Flower of Life.",
    "correctAnswer": "a Dragon Egg",
    "wrongAnswer": "the Flower of Life"
  },
  {
    "id": "94",
    "questionTemplate": "At the Cactus Plateau in Star Sand Desert, Moa King Kakkan is protecting ______",
    "correctQuestion": "At the Cactus Plateau in Star Sand Desert, Moa King Kakkan is protecting the Flower of Life.",
    "wrongQuestion": "At the Cactus Plateau in Star Sand Desert, Moa King Kakkan is protecting a Dragon Egg.",
    "correctAnswer": "the Flower of Life",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Dragon Egg"
  },
  {
    "id": "95",
    "questionTemplate": "The Treasure Hunt in Star Sand Desert is called the \"______ .",
    "correctQuestion": "The Treasure Hunt in Star Sand Desert is called the \"Star Plan\".",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Treasure Hunt in Star Sand Desert is called the \"Galaxy Plan\".",
    "correctAnswer": "Star Plan",
    "wrongAnswer": "Galaxy Plan"
  },
  {
    "id": "96",
    "questionTemplate": "The mercenaries at Cracked Sand Plain in Star Sand Desert are trembling due to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The mercenaries at Cracked Sand Plain in Star Sand Desert are trembling due to poisoning.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The mercenaries at Cracked Sand Plain in Star Sand Desert are trembling due to fear.",
    "correctAnswer": "poisoning",
    "wrongAnswer": "fear"
  },
  {
    "id": "97",
    "questionTemplate": "At the Temple of Sand, the expedition team discovers that ______ has beaten them there.",
    "correctQuestion": "At the Temple of Sand, the expedition team discovers that Caroline has beaten them there.",
    "wrongQuestion": "At the Temple of Sand, the expedition team discovers that Akara has beaten them there.",
    "correctAnswer": "Caroline",
    "wrongAnswer": "Akara"
  },
  {
    "id": "98",
    "questionTemplate": "Tatiana betrays the Makar because she ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Tatiana betrays the Makar because she is encouraged to do so by Micha.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Tatiana betrays the Makar because she hopes that Micha will become their leader.",
    "correctAnswer": "is encouraged to do so by Micha",
    "wrongAnswer": "hopes that Micha will become their leader"
  },
  {
    "id": "99",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, you enter Wrathborne Temple in Ventos Prairie to get ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, you enter Wrathborne Temple in Ventos Prairie to get Tears of Ares.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, you enter Wrathborne Temple in Ventos Prairie to get medicine.",
    "correctAnswer": "Tears of Ares",
    "wrongAnswer": "medicine"
  },
  {
    "id": "100",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, you bring the Orb to Wrathborne Temple in Ventos Prairie to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, you bring the Orb to Wrathborne Temple in Ventos Prairie to reseal the temple.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, you bring the Orb to Wrathborne Temple in Ventos Prairie to recover the power of the staff.",
    "correctAnswer": "reseal the temple",
    "wrongAnswer": "recover the power of the staff"
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Church contacts the Sanknie Alliance to get ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Church contacts the Sanknie Alliance to get financial support.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Main Quest storyline, the Church contacts the Sanknie Alliance to get military support.",
    "correctAnswer": "financial support",
    "wrongAnswer": "military support"
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "questionTemplate": "The Ruby Necklace stolen by Fleet Footed Adie belongs to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Ruby Necklace stolen by Fleet Footed Adie belongs to Star Sand Desert Travel Agent Seagram.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Ruby Necklace stolen by Fleet Footed Adie belongs to Banker Thorne.",
    "correctAnswer": "Star Sand Desert Travel Agent Seagram",
    "wrongAnswer": "Banker Thorne"
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "questionTemplate": "The gate of the city of Navea leads to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The gate of the city of Navea leads to Crescent Hill.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The gate of the city of Navea leads to Cactakara Forest.",
    "correctAnswer": "Crescent Hill",
    "wrongAnswer": "Cactakara Forest"
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "questionTemplate": "The necklace stolen from Banker Thorne was inlaid with a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The necklace stolen from Banker Thorne was inlaid with a Ruby.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The necklace stolen from Banker Thorne was inlaid with a Sapphire.",
    "correctAnswer": "Ruby",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sapphire"
  },
  {
    "id": "105",
    "questionTemplate": "Tribal Chief Taluda uses ______ powers.",
    "correctQuestion": "Tribal Chief Taluda uses Holy Flash powers.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Tribal Chief Taluda uses Storm powers.",
    "correctAnswer": "Holy Flash",
    "wrongAnswer": "Storm"
  },
  {
    "id": "106",
    "questionTemplate": "Tribal Chief Taluda is the leader of the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Tribal Chief Taluda is the leader of the Gnomes.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Tribal Chief Taluda is the leader of the Trolls.",
    "correctAnswer": "Gnomes",
    "wrongAnswer": "Trolls"
  },
  {
    "id": "107",
    "questionTemplate": "Rebel Leader Odum Ryan is actually the ______ Prince of the Makar in Ventos Prairie.",
    "correctQuestion": "Rebel Leader Odum Ryan is actually the third Prince of the Makar in Ventos Prairie.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Rebel Leader Odum Ryan is actually the second Prince of the Makar in Ventos Prairie.",
    "correctAnswer": "third",
    "wrongAnswer": "second"
  },
  {
    "id": "108",
    "questionTemplate": "Rebel Leader Odum Ryan wanted to aquire the power of the ______ temple.",
    "correctQuestion": "Rebel Leader Odum Ryan wanted to aquire the power of the Alabastren temple.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Rebel Leader Odum Ryan wanted to aquire the power of the Obsidian temple.",
    "correctAnswer": "Alabastren",
    "wrongAnswer": "Obsidian"
  },
  {
    "id": "109",
    "questionTemplate": "The cursed Envoy of Gaia in the Alabastren Temple is called ______ Correct Answer: win %s2 pts. No Answer: lose %s3 pts. Wrong Answer: lose %s4 pts.",
    "correctQuestion": "The cursed Envoy of Gaia in the Alabastren Temple is called Sonjuno.Correct Answer: win %s2 pts. No Answer: lose %s3 pts. Wrong Answer: lose %s4 pts.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The cursed Envoy of Gaia in the Alabastren Temple is called Sanjuro.Correct Answer: win %s2 pts. No Answer: lose %s3 pts. Wrong Answer: lose %s4 pts.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sonjuno",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sanjuro"
  },
  {
    "id": "110",
    "questionTemplate": "Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan attacks by throwing ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan attacks by throwing Bulbombs.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan attacks by throwing Bark Bombs.",
    "correctAnswer": "Bulbombs",
    "wrongAnswer": "Bark Bombs"
  },
  {
    "id": "111",
    "questionTemplate": "The bark of Otherworld Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The bark of Otherworld Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan is white.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The bark of Otherworld Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan is green.",
    "correctAnswer": "white",
    "wrongAnswer": "green"
  },
  {
    "id": "112",
    "questionTemplate": "The leaves of Otherworld Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The leaves of Otherworld Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan are red.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The leaves of Otherworld Glimmering Woodbeast Noripan are green.",
    "correctAnswer": "red",
    "wrongAnswer": "green"
  },
  {
    "id": "113",
    "questionTemplate": "Fia is the Princess of ______ Glen.",
    "correctQuestion": "Fia is the Princess of Gydaie Glen.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Fia is the Princess of Golden Glen.",
    "correctAnswer": "Gydaie",
    "wrongAnswer": "Golden"
  },
  {
    "id": "114",
    "questionTemplate": "The final boss in Gydaie Glen is Ancient ______ Kayel the Protector.",
    "correctQuestion": "The final boss in Gydaie Glen is Ancient Sawbot Kayel the Protector.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The final boss in Gydaie Glen is Ancient Smartbot Kayel the Protector.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sawbot",
    "wrongAnswer": "Smartbot"
  },
  {
    "id": "115",
    "questionTemplate": "Kayel the Protector in Gydaie Glen is a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Kayel the Protector in Gydaie Glen is a Robot.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Kayel the Protector in Gydaie Glen is a Mutant.",
    "correctAnswer": "Robot",
    "wrongAnswer": "Mutant"
  },
  {
    "id": "116",
    "questionTemplate": "Marauder Captain Qulun uses ______ to attack multiple enemies at the same time.",
    "correctQuestion": "Marauder Captain Qulun uses Blade Dance to attack multiple enemies at the same time.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Marauder Captain Qulun uses Furious Blade to attack multiple enemies at the same time.",
    "correctAnswer": "Blade Dance",
    "wrongAnswer": "Furious Blade"
  },
  {
    "id": "117",
    "questionTemplate": "Marauder Captain Qulun uses ______ blades.",
    "correctQuestion": "Marauder Captain Qulun uses 2 blades.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Marauder Captain Qulun uses 3 blades.",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "wrongAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "118",
    "questionTemplate": "Giant Crystal Beetle Ramgram attacks by spawning ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Giant Crystal Beetle Ramgram attacks by spawning Crystal Beetle Larvae.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Giant Crystal Beetle Ramgram attacks by spawning Iron Beetle Larvae.",
    "correctAnswer": "Crystal Beetle Larvae",
    "wrongAnswer": "Iron Beetle Larvae"
  },
  {
    "id": "119",
    "questionTemplate": "Giant Crystal Beetle Ramgram usually hides ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Giant Crystal Beetle Ramgram usually hides underground.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Giant Crystal Beetle Ramgram usually hides in a flower.",
    "correctAnswer": "underground",
    "wrongAnswer": "in a flower"
  },
  {
    "id": "120",
    "questionTemplate": "In Demarech Mines, Maggie summons ______ Titanius.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, Maggie summons Bloodface Titanius.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, Maggie summons Scarletface Titanius.",
    "correctAnswer": "Bloodface",
    "wrongAnswer": "Scarletface"
  },
  {
    "id": "121",
    "questionTemplate": "In Demarech Mines, Maggie releases ______ avatars to summon Titanius.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, Maggie releases 4 avatars to summon Titanius.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, Maggie releases 5 avatars to summon Titanius.",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "wrongAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "122",
    "questionTemplate": "Zaunna is the ______ of the cult in Deep's Cavern.",
    "correctQuestion": "Zaunna is the leader of the cult in Deep's Cavern.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Zaunna is the guide of the cult in Deep's Cavern.",
    "correctAnswer": "leader",
    "wrongAnswer": "guide"
  },
  {
    "id": "123",
    "questionTemplate": "At the bottom of Deep's Cavern lies ______ Adracei.",
    "correctQuestion": "At the bottom of Deep's Cavern lies Arachnid Queen Adracei.",
    "wrongQuestion": "At the bottom of Deep's Cavern lies Arachnid King Adracei.",
    "correctAnswer": "Arachnid Queen",
    "wrongAnswer": "Arachnid King"
  },
  {
    "id": "124",
    "questionTemplate": "Adracei in Deep's Cavern is a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Adracei in Deep's Cavern is a spider.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Adracei in Deep's Cavern is a crab.",
    "correctAnswer": "spider",
    "wrongAnswer": "crab"
  },
  {
    "id": "125",
    "questionTemplate": "Abyss Behemoth Argus attacks with ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Abyss Behemoth Argus attacks with fire.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Abyss Behemoth Argus attacks with ice.",
    "correctAnswer": "fire",
    "wrongAnswer": "ice"
  },
  {
    "id": "126",
    "questionTemplate": "Abyss Behemoth Argus is affected by the power of the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Abyss Behemoth Argus is affected by the power of the Cube of Gaia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Abyss Behemoth Argus is affected by the power of the Cube of Creation.",
    "correctAnswer": "Cube of Gaia",
    "wrongAnswer": "Cube of Creation"
  },
  {
    "id": "127",
    "questionTemplate": "Candeo Marsh Plauguebearer Lestaro is evolved from a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Candeo Marsh Plauguebearer Lestaro is evolved from a Mudling.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Candeo Marsh Plauguebearer Lestaro is evolved from a Slimeling.",
    "correctAnswer": "Mudling",
    "wrongAnswer": "Slimeling"
  },
  {
    "id": "128",
    "questionTemplate": "Candeo Marsh Plaguebearer Lestaro attacks with ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Candeo Marsh Plaguebearer Lestaro attacks with ice.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Candeo Marsh Plaguebearer Lestaro attacks with fire.",
    "correctAnswer": "ice",
    "wrongAnswer": "fire"
  },
  {
    "id": "129",
    "questionTemplate": "Abyss Patroller Toto is evolved from a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Abyss Patroller Toto is evolved from a Turtle.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Abyss Patroller Toto is evolved from a   Crab.",
    "correctAnswer": "Turtle",
    "wrongAnswer": "  Crab"
  },
  {
    "id": "130",
    "questionTemplate": "The title of Toto in Candeo Core is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The title of Toto in Candeo Core is Patroller.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The title of Toto in Candeo Core is President.",
    "correctAnswer": "Patroller",
    "wrongAnswer": "President"
  },
  {
    "id": "131",
    "questionTemplate": "Sarpa Queen Asheara summons ______ to attack enemies.",
    "correctQuestion": "Sarpa Queen Asheara summons Ice Totems to attack enemies.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Sarpa Queen Asheara summons Water Totems to attack enemies.",
    "correctAnswer": "Ice Totems",
    "wrongAnswer": "Water Totems"
  },
  {
    "id": "132",
    "questionTemplate": "Sarpa Queen Asheara summons ______ to heal herself.",
    "correctQuestion": "Sarpa Queen Asheara summons Water Totems to heal herself.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Sarpa Queen Asheara summons Ice Totems to heal herself.",
    "correctAnswer": "Water Totems",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ice Totems"
  },
  {
    "id": "133",
    "questionTemplate": "The title of Asheara in Candeo Core is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The title of Asheara in Candeo Core is Sarpa Queen.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The title of Asheara in Candeo Core is Sarpa Princess.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sarpa Queen",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sarpa Princess"
  },
  {
    "id": "134",
    "questionTemplate": "The ______ Prince of the Makar helps restore the seal of Wrathborne Temple.",
    "correctQuestion": "The second Prince of the Makar helps restore the seal of Wrathborne Temple.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The third Prince of the Makar helps restore the seal of Wrathborne Temple.",
    "correctAnswer": "second",
    "wrongAnswer": "third"
  },
  {
    "id": "135",
    "questionTemplate": "After leaving Wrathborne Temple, Para Ryan is trapped in a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "After leaving Wrathborne Temple, Para Ryan is trapped in a Crystal Prison.",
    "wrongQuestion": "After leaving Wrathborne Temple, Para Ryan is trapped in a Sealed Crystal.",
    "correctAnswer": "Crystal Prison",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sealed Crystal"
  },
  {
    "id": "136",
    "questionTemplate": "The left hand of Temporal Golem Kelosa is covered in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The left hand of Temporal Golem Kelosa is covered in fire.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The left hand of Temporal Golem Kelosa is covered in ice.",
    "correctAnswer": "fire",
    "wrongAnswer": "ice"
  },
  {
    "id": "137",
    "questionTemplate": "The right hand of Temporal Golem Kelosa is covered in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The right hand of Temporal Golem Kelosa is covered in ice.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The right hand of Temporal Golem Kelosa is covered in fire.",
    "correctAnswer": "ice",
    "wrongAnswer": "fire"
  },
  {
    "id": "139",
    "questionTemplate": "Holy Unicorn Saint Hale is protected by a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Holy Unicorn Saint Hale is protected by a Column of Light.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Holy Unicorn Saint Hale is protected by a Column of Colors.",
    "correctAnswer": "Column of Light",
    "wrongAnswer": "Column of Colors"
  },
  {
    "id": "140",
    "questionTemplate": "Saint Hale is a Holy ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Saint Hale is a Holy Unicorn.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Saint Hale is a Holy Pegasus.",
    "correctAnswer": "Unicorn",
    "wrongAnswer": "Pegasus"
  },
  {
    "id": "141",
    "questionTemplate": "Fallen Warrior Frederic is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Fallen Warrior Frederic is an Angel.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Fallen Warrior Frederic is a Demon.",
    "correctAnswer": "an Angel",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Demon"
  },
  {
    "id": "142",
    "questionTemplate": "The wings of Fallen Warrior Frederic are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The wings of Fallen Warrior Frederic are white.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The wings of Fallen Warrior Frederic are black.",
    "correctAnswer": "white",
    "wrongAnswer": "black"
  },
  {
    "id": "143",
    "questionTemplate": "Ghostweep Chameleon Gekasso swallows ______ Butterfly Fairies.",
    "correctQuestion": "Ghostweep Chameleon Gekasso swallows 3 Butterfly Fairies.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Ghostweep Chameleon Gekasso swallows 4 Butterfly Fairies.",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "144",
    "questionTemplate": "When you defeat Gekasso in Ghostweep Cave, ______ Butterfly Fairies escape.",
    "correctQuestion": "When you defeat Gekasso in Ghostweep Cave, 1 Butterfly Fairies escape.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When you defeat Gekasso in Ghostweep Cave, 2 Butterfly Fairies escape.",
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "wrongAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "145",
    "questionTemplate": "Ghostweep Chameleon Gekasso switches between ______ different colors.",
    "correctQuestion": "Ghostweep Chameleon Gekasso switches between 4 different colors.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Ghostweep Chameleon Gekasso switches between 3 different colors.",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "wrongAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "146",
    "questionTemplate": "Malodnak in Ghostweep Cave is a Zombie ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Malodnak in Ghostweep Cave is a Zombie Gatekeeper.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Malodnak in Ghostweep Cave is a Zombie Watchdog.",
    "correctAnswer": "Gatekeeper",
    "wrongAnswer": "Watchdog"
  },
  {
    "id": "147",
    "questionTemplate": "The Ghostweep Ruins Magic Source in Ghostweep Cave will transform Zombie Exiles into ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Ghostweep Ruins Magic Source in Ghostweep Cave will transform Zombie Exiles into Zombie Whippers.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Ghostweep Ruins Magic Source in Ghostweep Cave will transform Zombie Exiles into Zombie Thrashers.",
    "correctAnswer": "Zombie Whippers",
    "wrongAnswer": "Zombie Thrashers"
  },
  {
    "id": "148",
    "questionTemplate": "Duke of the Beyond Talen summons ______ Zombies when he appears.",
    "correctQuestion": "Duke of the Beyond Talen summons 6 Zombies when he appears.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Duke of the Beyond Talen summons 8 Zombies when he appears.",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "wrongAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "149",
    "questionTemplate": "Chief Guardian Murfeo protects the legendary ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Chief Guardian Murfeo protects the legendary Sand Gem.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Chief Guardian Murfeo protects the legendary Rock Gem.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sand Gem",
    "wrongAnswer": "Rock Gem"
  },
  {
    "id": "150",
    "questionTemplate": "Helakar is the Eidolon of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Helakar is the Eidolon of Caroline.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Helakar is the Eidolon of Katrina.",
    "correctAnswer": "Caroline",
    "wrongAnswer": "Katrina"
  },
  {
    "id": "151",
    "questionTemplate": "Immortal Demon Talamund's sworn enemy is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Immortal Demon Talamund's sworn enemy is Wrenna.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Immortal Demon Talamund's sworn enemy is Wynona.",
    "correctAnswer": "Wrenna",
    "wrongAnswer": "Wynona"
  },
  {
    "id": "152",
    "questionTemplate": "There are ______ levels in Infernal Abyss.",
    "correctQuestion": "There are 50 levels in Infernal Abyss.",
    "wrongQuestion": "There are 100 levels in Infernal Abyss.",
    "correctAnswer": "50",
    "wrongAnswer": "100"
  },
  {
    "id": "153",
    "questionTemplate": "After every ______ levels, Incarnation of Zaahir will appear in Infernal Abyss.",
    "correctQuestion": "After every 5 levels, Incarnation of Zaahir will appear in Infernal Abyss.",
    "wrongQuestion": "After every 10 levels, Incarnation of Zaahir will appear in Infernal Abyss.",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "wrongAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "154",
    "questionTemplate": "The sleeping Great Leviathan Nazrudin is protected by ______ waves of Disciples.",
    "correctQuestion": "The sleeping Great Leviathan Nazrudin is protected by 25 waves of Disciples.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The sleeping Great Leviathan Nazrudin is protected by 50 waves of Disciples.",
    "correctAnswer": "25",
    "wrongAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "id": "155",
    "questionTemplate": "In Whirlpool Abyss, Nazrudin Spawn will apear after every ______ waves of Disciples you defeat.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Whirlpool Abyss, Nazrudin Spawn will apear after every 5 waves of Disciples you defeat.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Whirlpool Abyss, Nazrudin Spawn will apear after every 10 waves of Disciples you defeat.",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "wrongAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "156",
    "questionTemplate": "Granny Rose lost her way near ______ in Navea.",
    "correctQuestion": "Granny Rose lost her way near Sky Tower in Navea.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Granny Rose lost her way near Castle Church in Navea.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sky Tower",
    "wrongAnswer": "Castle Church"
  },
  {
    "id": "157",
    "questionTemplate": "During the game of hide-and-seek, Mick's friend Allen is hidden ______",
    "correctQuestion": "During the game of hide-and-seek, Mick's friend Allen is hidden on the roof.",
    "wrongQuestion": "During the game of hide-and-seek, Mick's friend Allen is hidden in an alley.",
    "correctAnswer": "on the roof",
    "wrongAnswer": "in an alley"
  },
  {
    "id": "158",
    "questionTemplate": "In the city of Navea, Leroux trains newbies by having them attack ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the city of Navea, Leroux trains newbies by having them attack Wooden Dummies.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the city of Navea, Leroux trains newbies by having them attack Scarecrows.",
    "correctAnswer": "Wooden Dummies",
    "wrongAnswer": "Scarecrows"
  },
  {
    "id": "159",
    "questionTemplate": "Laura owns a ______ in the Trade District of Navea.",
    "correctQuestion": "Laura owns a bakery in the Trade District of Navea.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Laura owns a flower shop in the Trade District of Navea.",
    "correctAnswer": "bakery",
    "wrongAnswer": "flower shop"
  },
  {
    "id": "160",
    "questionTemplate": "The matchsticks sold by Wendy in Navea cost ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The matchsticks sold by Wendy in Navea cost 1 Silver.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The matchsticks sold by Wendy in Navea cost 10 Silver.",
    "correctAnswer": "1 Silver",
    "wrongAnswer": "10 Silver"
  },
  {
    "id": "161",
    "questionTemplate": "There is an ______ in Navea that can be used as a free sightseeing service.",
    "correctQuestion": "There is an Ostrich Carriage in Navea that can be used as a free sightseeing service.",
    "wrongQuestion": "There is an Ox Carriage in Navea that can be used as a free sightseeing service.",
    "correctAnswer": "Ostrich Carriage",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ox Carriage"
  },
  {
    "id": "162",
    "questionTemplate": "Delivery Person McArthur can't work because ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Delivery Person McArthur can't work because he hurt his foot.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Delivery Person McArthur can't work because he took an arrow to the knee.",
    "correctAnswer": "he hurt his foot",
    "wrongAnswer": "he took an arrow to the knee"
  },
  {
    "id": "163",
    "questionTemplate": "Taz the Fisherman has lost a ______ in the pool in Navea.",
    "correctQuestion": "Taz the Fisherman has lost a bag of money in the pool in Navea.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Taz the Fisherman has lost a golden fish in the pool in Navea.",
    "correctAnswer": "bag of money",
    "wrongAnswer": "golden fish"
  },
  {
    "id": "164",
    "questionTemplate": "The medical supplies in the cargo box in Port Skandia go to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The medical supplies in the cargo box in Port Skandia go to Village Doctor Cal.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The medical supplies in the cargo box in Port Skandia go to Warehouse Manager Bernie.",
    "correctAnswer": "Village Doctor Cal",
    "wrongAnswer": "Warehouse Manager Bernie"
  },
  {
    "id": "165",
    "questionTemplate": "Bunnyhops in Port Skandia like to eat ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Bunnyhops in Port Skandia like to eat cabbage.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Bunnyhops in Port Skandia like to eat carrots.",
    "correctAnswer": "cabbage",
    "wrongAnswer": "carrots"
  },
  {
    "id": "166",
    "questionTemplate": "The professional fisherman in Port Skandia catches a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The professional fisherman in Port Skandia catches a Large River Crab.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The professional fisherman in Port Skandia catches a Golden Fish.",
    "correctAnswer": "Large River Crab",
    "wrongAnswer": "Golden Fish"
  },
  {
    "id": "167",
    "questionTemplate": "Westen gives you a picture called \"______  as a reward for bringing him Common Sage.",
    "correctQuestion": "Westen gives you a picture called \"The Soaring Skies of Skandia\" as a reward for bringing him Common Sage.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Westen gives you a picture called \"Springtime in Skandia\" as a reward for bringing him Common Sage.",
    "correctAnswer": "The Soaring Skies of Skandia",
    "wrongAnswer": "Springtime in Skandia"
  },
  {
    "id": "168",
    "questionTemplate": "Flower's experiment turns a Sunbird into a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Flower's experiment turns a Sunbird into a Sunbird Egg.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Flower's experiment turns a Sunbird into a Giant Sunbird.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sunbird Egg",
    "wrongAnswer": "Giant Sunbird"
  },
  {
    "id": "169",
    "questionTemplate": "The \"most beautiful girl\" mentioned in the letter found at Helonia Coast is actually ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The \"most beautiful girl\" mentioned in the letter found at Helonia Coast is actually Solitary Woman.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The \"most beautiful girl\" mentioned in the letter found at Helonia Coast is actually Auntie May.",
    "correctAnswer": "Solitary Woman",
    "wrongAnswer": "Auntie May"
  },
  {
    "id": "170",
    "questionTemplate": "The Sneaky Villager of Helonia's true identity is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Sneaky Villager of Helonia's true identity is a Catseye Pirate Spy.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Sneaky Villager of Helonia's true identity is a Thief.",
    "correctAnswer": "a Catseye Pirate Spy",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Thief"
  },
  {
    "id": "171",
    "questionTemplate": "Green Juice and ______ are the materials mentioned in the Gnome makeup book.",
    "correctQuestion": "Green Juice and Birdbrain Feathers are the materials mentioned in the Gnome makeup book.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Green Juice and Beebis Feathers are the materials mentioned in the Gnome makeup book.",
    "correctAnswer": "Birdbrain Feathers",
    "wrongAnswer": "Beebis Feathers"
  },
  {
    "id": "172",
    "questionTemplate": "Carmichael's job at Helonia Coast is to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Carmichael's job at Helonia Coast is to keep the windmill working.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Carmichael's job at Helonia Coast is to predict earthquakes.",
    "correctAnswer": "keep the windmill working",
    "wrongAnswer": "predict earthquakes"
  },
  {
    "id": "173",
    "questionTemplate": "Ralph at Helonia Coast dreams of becoming a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Ralph at Helonia Coast dreams of becoming a Pirate King.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Ralph at Helonia Coast dreams of becoming a Pirate Admiral.",
    "correctAnswer": "Pirate King",
    "wrongAnswer": "Pirate Admiral"
  },
  {
    "id": "174",
    "questionTemplate": "Perry of Helonia Coast names his parrot ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Perry of Helonia Coast names his parrot Bobby.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Perry of Helonia Coast names his parrot Robbie.",
    "correctAnswer": "Bobby",
    "wrongAnswer": "Robbie"
  },
  {
    "id": "175",
    "questionTemplate": "Birdbrain Feathers and ______ are the materials mentioned in the Gnome makeup book.",
    "correctQuestion": "Birdbrain Feathers and Green Juice are the materials mentioned in the Gnome makeup book.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Birdbrain Feathers and Black Juice are the materials mentioned in the Gnome makeup book.",
    "correctAnswer": "Green Juice",
    "wrongAnswer": "Black Juice"
  },
  {
    "id": "176",
    "questionTemplate": "The Strange Beans around Crescent Hill grew into a ______ at Clark Farm.",
    "correctQuestion": "The Strange Beans around Crescent Hill grew into a Rainbow Beetle at Clark Farm.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Strange Beans around Crescent Hill grew into a Rainbow Flower at Clark Farm.",
    "correctAnswer": "Rainbow Beetle",
    "wrongAnswer": "Rainbow Flower"
  },
  {
    "id": "177",
    "questionTemplate": "Anthony of Crescent Hill needs Lion's Mane to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Anthony of Crescent Hill needs Lion's Mane to make his hair grow back.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Anthony of Crescent Hill needs Lion's Mane to make his beard grow back.",
    "correctAnswer": "make his hair grow back",
    "wrongAnswer": "make his beard grow back"
  },
  {
    "id": "178",
    "questionTemplate": "Gruff's Baby at Crescent Hill is a lovely ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Gruff's Baby at Crescent Hill is a lovely Jerboa.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Gruff's Baby at Crescent Hill is a lovely Bunnyhop.",
    "correctAnswer": "Jerboa",
    "wrongAnswer": "Bunnyhop"
  },
  {
    "id": "179",
    "questionTemplate": "When you give Moonlight Flower to Nala of Lunarin, she will give you ______ as a reward.",
    "correctQuestion": "When you give Moonlight Flower to Nala of Lunarin, she will give you Garland as a reward.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When you give Moonlight Flower to Nala of Lunarin, she will give you scarf as a reward.",
    "correctAnswer": "Garland",
    "wrongAnswer": "scarf"
  },
  {
    "id": "180",
    "questionTemplate": "The ______ in Cactakara Forest can be used as a fuel additive, dramatically increasing a machine's performance.",
    "correctQuestion": "The Grass Sprite Spores in Cactakara Forest can be used as a fuel additive, dramatically increasing a machine's performance.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Mechanical Power Core in Cactakara Forest can be used as a fuel additive, dramatically increasing a machine's performance.",
    "correctAnswer": "Grass Sprite Spores",
    "wrongAnswer": "Mechanical Power Core"
  },
  {
    "id": "181",
    "questionTemplate": "In Cactakara Forest, there is a goat named \"______  whose favorite food is apples.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Cactakara Forest, there is a goat named \"Princess\" whose favorite food is apples.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Cactakara Forest, there is a goat named \"Queenie\" whose favorite food is apples.",
    "correctAnswer": "Princess",
    "wrongAnswer": "Queenie"
  },
  {
    "id": "182",
    "questionTemplate": "If you practice meditating under the waterfall, you will receive the title of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "If you practice meditating under the waterfall, you will receive the title of Master of Meditations.",
    "wrongQuestion": "If you practice meditating under the waterfall, you will receive the title of Eternal Rising Sun.",
    "correctAnswer": "Master of Meditations",
    "wrongAnswer": "Eternal Rising Sun"
  },
  {
    "id": "183",
    "questionTemplate": "Posey of Cactakara Forest is searching for Purple Lotus to refine ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Posey of Cactakara Forest is searching for Purple Lotus to refine the ultimate fuel.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Posey of Cactakara Forest is searching for Purple Lotus to refine the ultimate elixir.",
    "correctAnswer": "the ultimate fuel",
    "wrongAnswer": "the ultimate elixir"
  },
  {
    "id": "184",
    "questionTemplate": "In Cactakara Forest, Stark's newest invention is ______  But it can't be used for the competition.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Cactakara Forest, Stark's newest invention is Iron Gear. But it can't be used for the competition.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Cactakara Forest, Stark's newest invention is Steel Gear. But it can't be used for the competition.",
    "correctAnswer": "Iron Gear",
    "wrongAnswer": "Steel Gear"
  },
  {
    "id": "185",
    "questionTemplate": "In Cactakara Forest, a goat named Princess loves to eat ______ more than anything.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Cactakara Forest, a goat named Princess loves to eat apples more than anything.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Cactakara Forest, a goat named Princess loves to eat corn more than anything.",
    "correctAnswer": "apples",
    "wrongAnswer": "corn"
  },
  {
    "id": "186",
    "questionTemplate": "The Pickaxe lost by the Miner in Tomitosa was a momento from his ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Pickaxe lost by the Miner in Tomitosa was a momento from his father.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Pickaxe lost by the Miner in Tomitosa was a momento from his grandfather.",
    "correctAnswer": "father",
    "wrongAnswer": "grandfather"
  },
  {
    "id": "187",
    "questionTemplate": "When you throw the Goddess Engraved Coin into Demarech Pool, the Goddess will ______",
    "correctQuestion": "When you throw the Goddess Engraved Coin into Demarech Pool, the Goddess will throw the coin back in your face.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When you throw the Goddess Engraved Coin into Demarech Pool, the Goddess will grant you a wish.",
    "correctAnswer": "throw the coin back in your face",
    "wrongAnswer": "grant you a wish"
  },
  {
    "id": "188",
    "questionTemplate": "The Miracle Rock Beetles in Demarech Mines grow bigger if hit by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Miracle Rock Beetles in Demarech Mines grow bigger if hit by a Shining Stone.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Miracle Rock Beetles in Demarech Mines grow bigger if hit by the Best Slingshot in the World.",
    "correctAnswer": "a Shining Stone",
    "wrongAnswer": "the Best Slingshot in the World"
  },
  {
    "id": "189",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Demarech Mines, you can find a special type of Miracle Stone called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Demarech Mines, you can find a special type of Miracle Stone called a Shining Stone.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Demarech Mines, you can find a special type of Miracle Stone called a Sage Stone.",
    "correctAnswer": "a Shining Stone",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Sage Stone"
  },
  {
    "id": "190",
    "questionTemplate": "The Scavenger Birds in Demarech Mines become enraged if attacked by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Scavenger Birds in Demarech Mines become enraged if attacked by the Best Slingshot in the World.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Scavenger Birds in Demarech Mines become enraged if attacked by a Shining Stone.",
    "correctAnswer": "the Best Slingshot in the World",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Shining Stone"
  },
  {
    "id": "191",
    "questionTemplate": "Near Demarech Pool you can find a Wilderness Survival Guide, which belongs to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Near Demarech Pool you can find a Wilderness Survival Guide, which belongs to Rebecca.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Near Demarech Pool you can find a Wilderness Survival Guide, which belongs to Luther.",
    "correctAnswer": "Rebecca",
    "wrongAnswer": "Luther"
  },
  {
    "id": "192",
    "questionTemplate": "The Wandering Villager in New Moon Hunting Grounds is chasing after ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Wandering Villager in New Moon Hunting Grounds is chasing after a great beauty who has eluded him for 3 days.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Wandering Villager in New Moon Hunting Grounds is chasing after his  grandmother who died last year.",
    "correctAnswer": "a great beauty who has eluded him for 3 days",
    "wrongAnswer": "his  grandmother who died last year"
  },
  {
    "id": "193",
    "questionTemplate": "When you use the Blowdart on the Stone Hammer Hunters in Triatio Highlands, they ______",
    "correctQuestion": "When you use the Blowdart on the Stone Hammer Hunters in Triatio Highlands, they take a cactus needle to the eye.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When you use the Blowdart on the Stone Hammer Hunters in Triatio Highlands, they take an arrow to the knee.",
    "correctAnswer": "take a cactus needle to the eye",
    "wrongAnswer": "take an arrow to the knee"
  },
  {
    "id": "194",
    "questionTemplate": "If your clean the Dusty Old Grail in Triatio Highlands, a Chalice Demon will appear and ______",
    "correctQuestion": "If your clean the Dusty Old Grail in Triatio Highlands, a Chalice Demon will appear and try to steal your soul.",
    "wrongQuestion": "If your clean the Dusty Old Grail in Triatio Highlands, a Chalice Demon will appear and grant three of your wishes.",
    "correctAnswer": "try to steal your soul",
    "wrongAnswer": "grant three of your wishes"
  },
  {
    "id": "195",
    "questionTemplate": "The specialty of Triatio Highlands, Cactus Ice, is made from Ice, Cactus Fruit and ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The specialty of Triatio Highlands, Cactus Ice, is made from Ice, Cactus Fruit and Honey.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The specialty of Triatio Highlands, Cactus Ice, is made from Ice, Cactus Fruit and Maple Syrup.",
    "correctAnswer": "Honey",
    "wrongAnswer": "Maple Syrup"
  },
  {
    "id": "196",
    "questionTemplate": "Marvin's comment on Stout Beef Stew is: %s1",
    "correctQuestion": "Marvin's comment on Stout Beef Stew is: \"Disgusting!\"",
    "wrongQuestion": "Marvin's comment on Stout Beef Stew is: \"Delicious!\"",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Disgusting!\"",
    "wrongAnswer": "\"Delicious!\""
  },
  {
    "id": "197",
    "questionTemplate": "The specialty of Demarech Mines, Candeo Mushrooms, are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The specialty of Demarech Mines, Candeo Mushrooms, are toxic and inedible.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The specialty of Demarech Mines, Candeo Mushrooms, are edible after being dried and well-seasoned.",
    "correctAnswer": "toxic and inedible",
    "wrongAnswer": "edible after being dried and well-seasoned"
  },
  {
    "id": "198",
    "questionTemplate": "Sterling feeds the Turtles because he ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Sterling feeds the Turtles because he wants a companion.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Sterling feeds the Turtles because he wants to defeat Schroeder.",
    "correctAnswer": "wants a companion",
    "wrongAnswer": "wants to defeat Schroeder"
  },
  {
    "id": "199",
    "questionTemplate": "In Candetonn, Penny uses ______ to test the spring water from Sarpa Abyss.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Candetonn, Penny uses a human test subject to test the spring water from Sarpa Abyss.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Candetonn, Penny uses a pH stick to test the spring water from Sarpa Abyss.",
    "correctAnswer": "a human test subject",
    "wrongAnswer": "a pH stick"
  },
  {
    "id": "200",
    "questionTemplate": "Investigator Charlie's favorite animals are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Investigator Charlie's favorite animals are Unicorns.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Investigator Charlie's favorite animals are Rabbits.",
    "correctAnswer": "Unicorns",
    "wrongAnswer": "Rabbits"
  },
  {
    "id": "201",
    "questionTemplate": "Slick of Candetonn uses Mud to build ______ to frighten the Demon.",
    "correctQuestion": "Slick of Candetonn uses Mud to build a monster to frighten the Demon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Slick of Candetonn uses Mud to build bombs to frighten the Demon.",
    "correctAnswer": "a monster",
    "wrongAnswer": "bombs"
  },
  {
    "id": "202",
    "questionTemplate": "Penny of Candetonn uses ______ to test the spring water from Sarpa Abyss.",
    "correctQuestion": "Penny of Candetonn uses a human test subject to test the spring water from Sarpa Abyss.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Penny of Candetonn uses a pH stick to test the spring water from Sarpa Abyss.",
    "correctAnswer": "a human test subject",
    "wrongAnswer": "a pH stick"
  },
  {
    "id": "203",
    "questionTemplate": "The Achievement you earn after finding the Braided Rope for Nico is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Achievement you earn after finding the Braided Rope for Nico is Wrath of the Lioness.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Achievement you earn after finding the Braided Rope for Nico is Fearsome.",
    "correctAnswer": "Wrath of the Lioness",
    "wrongAnswer": "Fearsome"
  },
  {
    "id": "204",
    "questionTemplate": "Placing the Makar Totem at the entrance to Oracle will ______ the Makar's morale.",
    "correctQuestion": "Placing the Makar Totem at the entrance to Oracle will boost the Makar's morale.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Placing the Makar Totem at the entrance to Oracle will decrease the Makar's morale.",
    "correctAnswer": "boost",
    "wrongAnswer": "decrease"
  },
  {
    "id": "205",
    "questionTemplate": "To gain the Blessing of Sprites in Ventos Prairie, you need to pray to ______ ancestral totems.",
    "correctQuestion": "To gain the Blessing of Sprites in Ventos Prairie, you need to pray to 3 ancestral totems.",
    "wrongQuestion": "To gain the Blessing of Sprites in Ventos Prairie, you need to pray to 4 ancestral totems.",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "206",
    "questionTemplate": "After helping Mosley catch the Jerboa in Ventos Prairie, you get ______ as a reward.",
    "correctQuestion": "After helping Mosley catch the Jerboa in Ventos Prairie, you get a Strange Skewer as a reward.",
    "wrongQuestion": "After helping Mosley catch the Jerboa in Ventos Prairie, you get a Dark Beer as a reward.",
    "correctAnswer": "a Strange Skewer",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Dark Beer"
  },
  {
    "id": "207",
    "questionTemplate": "The Oracle Tribe has a mysterious potion which makes Jerboa ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Oracle Tribe has a mysterious potion which makes Jerboa smaller.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Oracle Tribe has a mysterious potion which makes Jerboa faster.",
    "correctAnswer": "smaller",
    "wrongAnswer": "faster"
  },
  {
    "id": "208",
    "questionTemplate": "The Title you earn after finding the Braided Rope for Nico is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Title you earn after finding the Braided Rope for Nico is Fearsome.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Title you earn after finding the Braided Rope for Nico is Wrath of the Lioness.",
    "correctAnswer": "Fearsome",
    "wrongAnswer": "Wrath of the Lioness"
  },
  {
    "id": "209",
    "questionTemplate": "In Ventos Prairie, Ahketa needs you to collect hair from a ______ to make artificial manes for his disgraced brethren.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Ventos Prairie, Ahketa needs you to collect hair from a Shaggy Hoofbeast to make artificial manes for his disgraced brethren.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Ventos Prairie, Ahketa needs you to collect hair from a Bloodthirsty Wolf to make artificial manes for his disgraced brethren.",
    "correctAnswer": "Shaggy Hoofbeast",
    "wrongAnswer": "Bloodthirsty Wolf"
  },
  {
    "id": "210",
    "questionTemplate": "The package that Drew lost during his escape contains ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The package that Drew lost during his escape contains a small pillow.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The package that Drew lost during his escape contains his Grandmother's necklace.",
    "correctAnswer": "a small pillow",
    "wrongAnswer": "his Grandmother's necklace"
  },
  {
    "id": "211",
    "questionTemplate": "Marty's comment on the Mysterious Cactus Fruit is: %s1",
    "correctQuestion": "Marty's comment on the Mysterious Cactus Fruit is: \"It tastes the same as any other cactus fruit!\"",
    "wrongQuestion": "Marty's comment on the Mysterious Cactus Fruit is: \"How unique!\"",
    "correctAnswer": "\"It tastes the same as any other cactus fruit!\"",
    "wrongAnswer": "\"How unique!\""
  },
  {
    "id": "212",
    "questionTemplate": "If you don't help Lamarr of Oblitus Wood get his Work Hat, he might ______",
    "correctQuestion": "If you don't help Lamarr of Oblitus Wood get his Work Hat, he might go crazy.",
    "wrongQuestion": "If you don't help Lamarr of Oblitus Wood get his Work Hat, he might take an arrow to the knee.",
    "correctAnswer": "go crazy",
    "wrongAnswer": "take an arrow to the knee"
  },
  {
    "id": "213",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is the mother of poor forgotten little Sidney.",
    "correctQuestion": "Marissa is the mother of poor forgotten little Sidney.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Fulla is the mother of poor forgotten little Sidney.",
    "correctAnswer": "Marissa",
    "wrongAnswer": "Fulla"
  },
  {
    "id": "214",
    "questionTemplate": "Dwight of Oblitus Wood hid himself in a cart to escape. He finally arrived in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Dwight of Oblitus Wood hid himself in a cart to escape. He finally arrived in Krok Village.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Dwight of Oblitus Wood hid himself in a cart to escape. He finally arrived in Nudak Fortress.",
    "correctAnswer": "Krok Village",
    "wrongAnswer": "Nudak Fortress"
  },
  {
    "id": "215",
    "questionTemplate": "The real name of the compass found in Sand Owl Camp is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The real name of the compass found in Sand Owl Camp is Star Sand Compass.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The real name of the compass found in Sand Owl Camp is Star Ocean Compass.",
    "correctAnswer": "Star Sand Compass",
    "wrongAnswer": "Star Ocean Compass"
  },
  {
    "id": "216",
    "questionTemplate": "Derek of Oblitus Wood wants to set up an instrument at the top of the mountain that will ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Derek of Oblitus Wood wants to set up an instrument at the top of the mountain that will detect approaching monsters.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Derek of Oblitus Wood wants to set up an instrument at the top of the mountain that will measure wind speed.",
    "correctAnswer": "detect approaching monsters",
    "wrongAnswer": "measure wind speed"
  },
  {
    "id": "217",
    "questionTemplate": "In Star Sand Desert, Desert Jerboas can be found ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, Desert Jerboas can be found north of Palmgil Oasis.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, Desert Jerboas can be found south of Cracked Sand Plain.",
    "correctAnswer": "north of Palmgil Oasis",
    "wrongAnswer": "south of Cracked Sand Plain"
  },
  {
    "id": "218",
    "questionTemplate": "Ada of Star Sand Desert thinks the thieves' code in the treasure cave is \"______",
    "correctQuestion": "Ada of Star Sand Desert thinks the thieves' code in the treasure cave is \"Open Biscuits!\"",
    "wrongQuestion": "Ada of Star Sand Desert thinks the thieves' code in the treasure cave is \"Open Sesame!\"",
    "correctAnswer": "Open Biscuits!",
    "wrongAnswer": "Open Sesame!"
  },
  {
    "id": "219",
    "questionTemplate": "The Delicious Cactoid mentioned by Marvin calls himself ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Delicious Cactoid mentioned by Marvin calls himself Mysterious Cactoid.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Delicious Cactoid mentioned by Marvin calls himself Cactoid King.",
    "correctAnswer": "Mysterious Cactoid",
    "wrongAnswer": "Cactoid King"
  },
  {
    "id": "220",
    "questionTemplate": "According to information found in the worn treasure chest in Star Sand Desert, the \"white sand\" is actually ______",
    "correctQuestion": "According to information found in the worn treasure chest in Star Sand Desert, the \"white sand\" is actually a waterfall.",
    "wrongQuestion": "According to information found in the worn treasure chest in Star Sand Desert, the \"white sand\" is actually snow.",
    "correctAnswer": "a waterfall",
    "wrongAnswer": "snow"
  },
  {
    "id": "221",
    "questionTemplate": "In Star Sand Desert, the Expedition Team Leader is named ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, the Expedition Team Leader is named Bernard.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, the Expedition Team Leader is named Bertrand.",
    "correctAnswer": "Bernard",
    "wrongAnswer": "Bertrand"
  },
  {
    "id": "222",
    "questionTemplate": "In Crescent Hill, Cass ______ Holly's invitation to the Crescent Ceremony.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Crescent Hill, Cass accepts Holly's invitation to the Crescent Ceremony.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Crescent Hill, Cass rejects Holly's invitation to the Crescent Ceremony.",
    "correctAnswer": "accepts",
    "wrongAnswer": "rejects"
  },
  {
    "id": "223",
    "questionTemplate": "Maddy wants to have ______ skin like the fairies.",
    "correctQuestion": "Maddy wants to have green skin like the fairies.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Maddy wants to have purple skin like the fairies.",
    "correctAnswer": "green",
    "wrongAnswer": "purple"
  },
  {
    "id": "224",
    "questionTemplate": "Kevin of Crescent Hill ______ bananas.",
    "correctQuestion": "Kevin of Crescent Hill hates bananas.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Kevin of Crescent Hill loves bananas.",
    "correctAnswer": "hates",
    "wrongAnswer": "loves"
  },
  {
    "id": "225",
    "questionTemplate": "Kristin of Cactakara Forest keeps waking up because Reuben ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Kristin of Cactakara Forest keeps waking up because Reuben makes too much noise repairing machines.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Kristin of Cactakara Forest keeps waking up because Reuben snores too loudly.",
    "correctAnswer": "makes too much noise repairing machines",
    "wrongAnswer": "snores too loudly"
  },
  {
    "id": "226",
    "questionTemplate": "Mary of Cactakara Forest wishes to the giant rainbow for ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Mary of Cactakara Forest wishes to the giant rainbow for another wish.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Mary of Cactakara Forest wishes to the giant rainbow for all the rainbow candies in the world.",
    "correctAnswer": "another wish",
    "wrongAnswer": "all the rainbow candies in the world"
  },
  {
    "id": "227",
    "questionTemplate": "Pam and Danielle of Cactakara Forest bet ______ candies.",
    "correctQuestion": "Pam and Danielle of Cactakara Forest bet 20 candies.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Pam and Danielle of Cactakara Forest bet 10 candies.",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "wrongAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "228",
    "questionTemplate": "The Legendary Craftsman, who Ted met in Cactakara Forest, is famous for ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Legendary Craftsman, who Ted met in Cactakara Forest, is famous for breaking everything he repairs.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Legendary Craftsman, who Ted met in Cactakara Forest, is famous for his glowing hands.",
    "correctAnswer": "breaking everything he repairs",
    "wrongAnswer": "his glowing hands"
  },
  {
    "id": "229",
    "questionTemplate": "Jane of Triatio Highlands wants to ______ with Connor.",
    "correctQuestion": "Jane of Triatio Highlands wants to travel the world with Connor.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Jane of Triatio Highlands wants to build a cozy little farm in her hometown with Connor.",
    "correctAnswer": "travel the world",
    "wrongAnswer": "build a cozy little farm in her hometown"
  },
  {
    "id": "230",
    "questionTemplate": "Emeline and Jeffen of Triatio Highlands ae ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Emeline and Jeffen of Triatio Highlands ae archaeologists.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Emeline and Jeffen of Triatio Highlands ae biologists.",
    "correctAnswer": "archaeologists",
    "wrongAnswer": "biologists"
  },
  {
    "id": "231",
    "questionTemplate": "Jerry and Nikki of Triatio Highlands are playing ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Jerry and Nikki of Triatio Highlands are playing in the sand.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Jerry and Nikki of Triatio Highlands are playing hide-and-seek.",
    "correctAnswer": "in the sand",
    "wrongAnswer": "hide-and-seek"
  },
  {
    "id": "232",
    "questionTemplate": "Ernest had a big fight with his wife because of his ______ Gustav.",
    "correctQuestion": "Ernest had a big fight with his wife because of his good friend Gustav.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Ernest had a big fight with his wife because of his mortal enemy Gustav.",
    "correctAnswer": "good friend",
    "wrongAnswer": "mortal enemy"
  },
  {
    "id": "233",
    "questionTemplate": "In Candeo Marsh, Gustav left the village to ______ Ernest.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Candeo Marsh, Gustav left the village to heal Ernest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Candeo Marsh, Gustav left the village to escape from Ernest.",
    "correctAnswer": "heal",
    "wrongAnswer": "escape from"
  },
  {
    "id": "234",
    "questionTemplate": "In Candeo Marsh, Dora made Mickey cry by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Candeo Marsh, Dora made Mickey cry by playing jokes on him.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Candeo Marsh, Dora made Mickey cry by confessing her love for him.",
    "correctAnswer": "playing jokes on him",
    "wrongAnswer": "confessing her love for him"
  },
  {
    "id": "235",
    "questionTemplate": "In Ventos Prairie, Quenton flirted desperately with Alanna. All of his effort finally ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Ventos Prairie, Quenton flirted desperately with Alanna. All of his effort finally failed.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Ventos Prairie, Quenton flirted desperately with Alanna. All of his effort finally won her over.",
    "correctAnswer": "failed",
    "wrongAnswer": "won her over"
  },
  {
    "id": "236",
    "questionTemplate": "In Ventos Prairie, Sandro and Woods decided to ______ to relive their childhood.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Ventos Prairie, Sandro and Woods decided to fly kites to relive their childhood.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Ventos Prairie, Sandro and Woods decided to roll around in the grass to relive their childhood.",
    "correctAnswer": "fly kites",
    "wrongAnswer": "roll around in the grass"
  },
  {
    "id": "237",
    "questionTemplate": "In Ventos Prairie, Ivy helped to find the lost ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Ventos Prairie, Ivy helped to find the lost necklace.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Ventos Prairie, Ivy helped to find the lost earring.",
    "correctAnswer": "necklace",
    "wrongAnswer": "earring"
  },
  {
    "id": "238",
    "questionTemplate": "In Oblitus Wood, Monty worries a lot about ______ who went to Ghostweep Cave.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Monty worries a lot about Shaine who went to Ghostweep Cave.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Monty worries a lot about Dominic who went to Ghostweep Cave.",
    "correctAnswer": "Shaine",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dominic"
  },
  {
    "id": "239",
    "questionTemplate": "In Oblitus Wood, Shaine wants to ______ Shana when he returns to the village.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Shaine wants to propose to Shana when he returns to the village.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Shaine wants to break up with Shana when he returns to the village.",
    "correctAnswer": "propose to",
    "wrongAnswer": "break up with"
  },
  {
    "id": "240",
    "questionTemplate": "In Oblitus Wood, Cody  went looking for her ______ despite the danger.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Cody  went looking for her pet cow despite the danger.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Cody  went looking for her boyfriend despite the danger.",
    "correctAnswer": "pet cow",
    "wrongAnswer": "boyfriend"
  },
  {
    "id": "241",
    "questionTemplate": "In Oblitus Wood, Auburn planned to take the ______ that his wife had hidden from him.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Auburn planned to take the gold coins that his wife had hidden from him.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Auburn planned to take the biscuits that his wife had hidden from him.",
    "correctAnswer": "gold coins",
    "wrongAnswer": "biscuits"
  },
  {
    "id": "242",
    "questionTemplate": "In Star Sand Desert, Posey's Treasure Map is actually Guy's ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, Posey's Treasure Map is actually Guy's random doodling.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, Posey's Treasure Map is actually Guy's old photo.",
    "correctAnswer": "random doodling",
    "wrongAnswer": "old photo"
  },
  {
    "id": "243",
    "questionTemplate": "In Star Sand Desert, Powell plans to leave ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, Powell plans to leave together with Phillip.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, Powell plans to leave without telling Phillip.",
    "correctAnswer": "together with Phillip",
    "wrongAnswer": "without telling Phillip"
  },
  {
    "id": "244",
    "questionTemplate": "Hank of Star Sand Desert wants to become a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Hank of Star Sand Desert wants to become a King of Thieves.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Hank of Star Sand Desert wants to become a Pirate King.",
    "correctAnswer": "King of Thieves",
    "wrongAnswer": "Pirate King"
  },
  {
    "id": "245",
    "questionTemplate": "Sheila of Star Sand Desert thinks that Maxim is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Sheila of Star Sand Desert thinks that Maxim is kind and responsible.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Sheila of Star Sand Desert thinks that Maxim is a complete idiot.",
    "correctAnswer": "kind and responsible",
    "wrongAnswer": "a complete idiot"
  },
  {
    "id": "246",
    "questionTemplate": "Romeo and Juliet are in ______ when they decide to travel together.",
    "correctQuestion": "Romeo and Juliet are in Port Skandia when they decide to travel together.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Romeo and Juliet are in Helonia Coast when they decide to travel together.",
    "correctAnswer": "Port Skandia",
    "wrongAnswer": "Helonia Coast"
  },
  {
    "id": "247",
    "questionTemplate": "Kenny of Port Skandia only eats ______ fish.",
    "correctQuestion": "Kenny of Port Skandia only eats roast fish.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Kenny of Port Skandia only eats boiled fish.",
    "correctAnswer": "roast",
    "wrongAnswer": "boiled"
  },
  {
    "id": "248",
    "questionTemplate": "In Port Skandia, the dishonest vegetable seller charges ______ gold for his green vegetables.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Port Skandia, the dishonest vegetable seller charges 81000 gold for his green vegetables.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Port Skandia, the dishonest vegetable seller charges 18000 gold for his green vegetables.",
    "correctAnswer": "81000",
    "wrongAnswer": "18000"
  },
  {
    "id": "249",
    "questionTemplate": "In Port Skandia, ______ worries that he will go bald.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Port Skandia, Sam worries that he will go bald.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Port Skandia, Peter worries that he will go bald.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sam",
    "wrongAnswer": "Peter"
  },
  {
    "id": "250",
    "questionTemplate": "The First Mate in Helonia Coast doesn't care about women because ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The First Mate in Helonia Coast doesn't care about women because a brotherhood doesn't need women.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The First Mate in Helonia Coast doesn't care about women because women are too much trouble.",
    "correctAnswer": "a brotherhood doesn't need women",
    "wrongAnswer": "women are too much trouble"
  },
  {
    "id": "251",
    "questionTemplate": "In Helonia Coast, Romeo and Juliet get romantic ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Helonia Coast, Romeo and Juliet get romantic at the beach.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Helonia Coast, Romeo and Juliet get romantic in the grassland.",
    "correctAnswer": "at the beach",
    "wrongAnswer": "in the grassland"
  },
  {
    "id": "252",
    "questionTemplate": "Lazy Alan of Helonia Coast is actually responsible for ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Lazy Alan of Helonia Coast is actually responsible for delivering fertilizer.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Lazy Alan of Helonia Coast is actually responsible for taking care of the fruit trees.",
    "correctAnswer": "delivering fertilizer",
    "wrongAnswer": "taking care of the fruit trees"
  },
  {
    "id": "253",
    "questionTemplate": "In Helonia Coast, Anna got the apples for ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Helonia Coast, Anna got the apples for free.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Helonia Coast, Anna got the apples for only 5 gold.",
    "correctAnswer": "free",
    "wrongAnswer": "only 5 gold"
  },
  {
    "id": "254",
    "questionTemplate": "In Demarech Mines, Merilee brings his brother to search for Crystal Ore to their ailing ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, Merilee brings his brother to search for Crystal Ore to their ailing Grandmother.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, Merilee brings his brother to search for Crystal Ore to their ailing Mother.",
    "correctAnswer": "Grandmother",
    "wrongAnswer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "id": "255",
    "questionTemplate": "The specialty of Demarech Mines is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The specialty of Demarech Mines is Ecstasy Fruit.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The specialty of Demarech Mines is Ecstasy Rice.",
    "correctAnswer": "Ecstasy Fruit",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ecstasy Rice"
  },
  {
    "id": "256",
    "questionTemplate": "Father Bo and Mother Bo of Demarech Mines have ______ children.",
    "correctQuestion": "Father Bo and Mother Bo of Demarech Mines have 6 children.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Father Bo and Mother Bo of Demarech Mines have 7 children.",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "wrongAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "257",
    "questionTemplate": "To earn the title of \"Dancer,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "To earn the title of \"Dancer,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of Crescent Hill.",
    "wrongQuestion": "To earn the title of \"Dancer,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of Demarech Mines.",
    "correctAnswer": "Crescent Hill",
    "wrongAnswer": "Demarech Mines"
  },
  {
    "id": "258",
    "questionTemplate": "To earn the title of \"Forest Hunter,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "To earn the title of \"Forest Hunter,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of Cactakara Forest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "To earn the title of \"Forest Hunter,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of Oblitus Wood.",
    "correctAnswer": "Cactakara Forest",
    "wrongAnswer": "Oblitus Wood"
  },
  {
    "id": "259",
    "questionTemplate": "To earn the title of \"World Traveler,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "To earn the title of \"World Traveler,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of Oblitus Wood.",
    "wrongQuestion": "To earn the title of \"World Traveler,\" you have to listen carefully to the stories from the people of Star Sand Desert.",
    "correctAnswer": "Oblitus Wood",
    "wrongAnswer": "Star Sand Desert"
  },
  {
    "id": "260",
    "questionTemplate": "You can complete the achievement \"Star Crossed\" in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "You can complete the achievement \"Star Crossed\" in Triatio Highlands.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can complete the achievement \"Star Crossed\" in Candeo Marsh.",
    "correctAnswer": "Triatio Highlands",
    "wrongAnswer": "Candeo Marsh"
  },
  {
    "id": "261",
    "questionTemplate": "You can complete the achievement \"Forbidden Love\" in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "You can complete the achievement \"Forbidden Love\" in Ventos Prairie.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can complete the achievement \"Forbidden Love\" in Helonia Coast.",
    "correctAnswer": "Ventos Prairie",
    "wrongAnswer": "Helonia Coast"
  },
  {
    "id": "262",
    "questionTemplate": "You can complete Achievement \"______  after listening to the conversation between the Younger Practitioner and the Older Practitioner in Cactakara Forest.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can complete Achievement \"That Takes Dedication\" after listening to the conversation between the Younger Practitioner and the Older Practitioner in Cactakara Forest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can complete Achievement \"Training...\" after listening to the conversation between the Younger Practitioner and the Older Practitioner in Cactakara Forest.",
    "correctAnswer": "That Takes Dedication",
    "wrongAnswer": "Training..."
  },
  {
    "id": "263",
    "questionTemplate": "You can complete achievement \"______  by listening in as Jeffen searches for clues in Triatio Highlands.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can complete achievement \"Broken Hopes\" by listening in as Jeffen searches for clues in Triatio Highlands.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can complete achievement \"Salvaged Dreams\" by listening in as Jeffen searches for clues in Triatio Highlands.",
    "correctAnswer": "Broken Hopes",
    "wrongAnswer": "Salvaged Dreams"
  },
  {
    "id": "264",
    "questionTemplate": "In the achievement \"Anything For Love,\" you learned that ______ was beaten up in Star Sand Desert.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the achievement \"Anything For Love,\" you learned that Romeo was beaten up in Star Sand Desert.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the achievement \"Anything For Love,\" you learned that Juliet was beaten up in Star Sand Desert.",
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo",
    "wrongAnswer": "Juliet"
  },
  {
    "id": "265",
    "questionTemplate": "The Mushroom Girl appears in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Mushroom Girl appears in Helonia Coast.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Mushroom Girl appears in Port Skandia.",
    "correctAnswer": "Helonia Coast",
    "wrongAnswer": "Port Skandia"
  },
  {
    "id": "266",
    "questionTemplate": "Navea's specialty is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Navea's specialty is Navea Special Roast Tea.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Navea's specialty is Clark's Fresh Milk.",
    "correctAnswer": "Navea Special Roast Tea",
    "wrongAnswer": "Clark's Fresh Milk"
  },
  {
    "id": "267",
    "questionTemplate": "You can gather ______ from the Stardust Flower Bush.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can gather Stardust Flowers from the Stardust Flower Bush.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can gather Ghost Peppers from the Stardust Flower Bush.",
    "correctAnswer": "Stardust Flowers",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ghost Peppers"
  },
  {
    "id": "268",
    "questionTemplate": "Helonia's specialty is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Helonia's specialty is Helonian Fruit Jelly.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Helonia's specialty is Navea Special Roast Tea.",
    "correctAnswer": "Helonian Fruit Jelly",
    "wrongAnswer": "Navea Special Roast Tea"
  },
  {
    "id": "269",
    "questionTemplate": "You can gather ______ from the Stardust Flower Bush.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can gather Fragrant Flowers from the Stardust Flower Bush.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can gather Giant Egg from the Stardust Flower Bush.",
    "correctAnswer": "Fragrant Flowers",
    "wrongAnswer": "Giant Egg"
  },
  {
    "id": "270",
    "questionTemplate": "The specialty of Lunarin in Crescent Hill is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The specialty of Lunarin in Crescent Hill is Crescent Hill Tea.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The specialty of Lunarin in Crescent Hill is Murky Coffee.",
    "correctAnswer": "Crescent Hill Tea",
    "wrongAnswer": "Murky Coffee"
  },
  {
    "id": "271",
    "questionTemplate": "You can gather ______ from the Nut Trees.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can gather Chopped Nuts from the Nut Trees.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can gather Mushrooms from the Nut Trees.",
    "correctAnswer": "Chopped Nuts",
    "wrongAnswer": "Mushrooms"
  },
  {
    "id": "272",
    "questionTemplate": "The ingredients for Dragon Soul Energy Drink are Beary Refreshing Drink and ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The ingredients for Dragon Soul Energy Drink are Beary Refreshing Drink and Vigor Leaves.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The ingredients for Dragon Soul Energy Drink are Beary Refreshing Drink and Flower Biscuit.",
    "correctAnswer": "Vigor Leaves",
    "wrongAnswer": "Flower Biscuit"
  },
  {
    "id": "273",
    "questionTemplate": "You can gather ______ from the Oasis Spice Bush.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can gather Oasis Spices from the Oasis Spice Bush.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can gather Oasis Beer from the Oasis Spice Bush.",
    "correctAnswer": "Oasis Spices",
    "wrongAnswer": "Oasis Beer"
  },
  {
    "id": "274",
    "questionTemplate": "You can gather ______ from the Highland Wheat Plants in Triatio Highlands.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can gather Highland Wheat from the Highland Wheat Plants in Triatio Highlands.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can gather Highland Wheat Flour from the Highland Wheat Plants in Triatio Highlands.",
    "correctAnswer": "Highland Wheat",
    "wrongAnswer": "Highland Wheat Flour"
  },
  {
    "id": "275",
    "questionTemplate": "The specialty of Candeo Marsh is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The specialty of Candeo Marsh is Murky Coffee.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The specialty of Candeo Marsh is Highland Buffalo Milk.",
    "correctAnswer": "Murky Coffee",
    "wrongAnswer": "Highland Buffalo Milk"
  },
  {
    "id": "276",
    "questionTemplate": "You can gather ______ from the Wind Spice Bush.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can gather Green Allspice from the Wind Spice Bush.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can gather Miracle Thornapple from the Wind Spice Bush.",
    "correctAnswer": "Green Allspice",
    "wrongAnswer": "Miracle Thornapple"
  },
  {
    "id": "277",
    "questionTemplate": "According to Ventos Sommelier Kronk, the best beer is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "According to Ventos Sommelier Kronk, the best beer is a Dark Beer.",
    "wrongQuestion": "According to Ventos Sommelier Kronk, the best beer is Oasis Beer.",
    "correctAnswer": "a Dark Beer",
    "wrongAnswer": "Oasis Beer"
  },
  {
    "id": "278",
    "questionTemplate": "In Oblitus Wood, Nudak Cook Lizzy's favorite food is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Nudak Cook Lizzy's favorite food is Sweet 'n Sour Meatballs.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Oblitus Wood, Nudak Cook Lizzy's favorite food is Mini Meatballs.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sweet 'n Sour Meatballs",
    "wrongAnswer": "Mini Meatballs"
  },
  {
    "id": "279",
    "questionTemplate": "In Forest Oblitus, Nudak Cook Lizzy and Apprentice Brewer Summer are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Forest Oblitus, Nudak Cook Lizzy and Apprentice Brewer Summer are siblings.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Forest Oblitus, Nudak Cook Lizzy and Apprentice Brewer Summer are a couple.",
    "correctAnswer": "siblings",
    "wrongAnswer": "a couple"
  },
  {
    "id": "280",
    "questionTemplate": "In Star Sand Desert, Palmgil Baker Doyle and Beverage Merchant Barney are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, Palmgil Baker Doyle and Beverage Merchant Barney are siblings.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Star Sand Desert, Palmgil Baker Doyle and Beverage Merchant Barney are a couple.",
    "correctAnswer": "siblings",
    "wrongAnswer": "a couple"
  },
  {
    "id": "281",
    "questionTemplate": "You complete the Achievement \"______  by defeating Destroyer Wade in Helonia Coast.",
    "correctQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Wrecking Ball\" by defeating Destroyer Wade in Helonia Coast.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"All In the Details\" by defeating Destroyer Wade in Helonia Coast.",
    "correctAnswer": "Wrecking Ball",
    "wrongAnswer": "All In the Details"
  },
  {
    "id": "282",
    "questionTemplate": "You complete the Achievement \"______  by defeating Doniland The Glutton in Helonia Coast.",
    "correctQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"See-Food Diet\" by defeating Doniland The Glutton in Helonia Coast.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Appetite Overload\" by defeating Doniland The Glutton in Helonia Coast.",
    "correctAnswer": "See-Food Diet",
    "wrongAnswer": "Appetite Overload"
  },
  {
    "id": "283",
    "questionTemplate": "You complete the Achievement \"______  by defeating the rare elite monsters of Cactakara Forest.",
    "correctQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Cactakara Curator\" by defeating the rare elite monsters of Cactakara Forest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Hero of Demarech Mines\" by defeating the rare elite monsters of Cactakara Forest.",
    "correctAnswer": "Cactakara Curator",
    "wrongAnswer": "Hero of Demarech Mines"
  },
  {
    "id": "284",
    "questionTemplate": "You complete the Achievement \"______  by defeating <Cruel Blood> Galen in Demarech Mines.",
    "correctQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Thirst For Blood\" by defeating <Cruel Blood> Galen in Demarech Mines.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Thirst For Beer\" by defeating <Cruel Blood> Galen in Demarech Mines.",
    "correctAnswer": "Thirst For Blood",
    "wrongAnswer": "Thirst For Beer"
  },
  {
    "id": "285",
    "questionTemplate": "You complete the Achievement \"______  by defeating \"Thousand-Needle\" Stingey in Triatio Highlands.",
    "correctQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Effective Lure\" by defeating \"Thousand-Needle\" Stingey in Triatio Highlands.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Hot Stuff\" by defeating \"Thousand-Needle\" Stingey in Triatio Highlands.",
    "correctAnswer": "Effective Lure",
    "wrongAnswer": "Hot Stuff"
  },
  {
    "id": "286",
    "questionTemplate": "You complete the Achievement \"______  by defeating the rare elite monsters of Candeo Marsh.",
    "correctQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Marsh Madness\" by defeating the rare elite monsters of Candeo Marsh.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Martian Madness\" by defeating the rare elite monsters of Candeo Marsh.",
    "correctAnswer": "Marsh Madness",
    "wrongAnswer": "Martian Madness"
  },
  {
    "id": "287",
    "questionTemplate": "You complete the Achievement \"______  by defeating \"Iron Wall\" Kelosa in Star Sand Desert.",
    "correctQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Armed to the Teeth\" by defeating \"Iron Wall\" Kelosa in Star Sand Desert.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You complete the Achievement \"Ghostly Tremors\" by defeating \"Iron Wall\" Kelosa in Star Sand Desert.",
    "correctAnswer": "Armed to the Teeth",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ghostly Tremors"
  },
  {
    "id": "288",
    "questionTemplate": "The Achievement you complete by completing your first kill is \"______ .",
    "correctQuestion": "The Achievement you complete by completing your first kill is \"Blood On Your Hands\".",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Achievement you complete by completing your first kill is \"Brimming With Potential\".",
    "correctAnswer": "Blood On Your Hands",
    "wrongAnswer": "Brimming With Potential"
  },
  {
    "id": "289",
    "questionTemplate": "To complete the Achievement \"Desensitized\", you need to complete ______ kills.",
    "correctQuestion": "To complete the Achievement \"Desensitized\", you need to complete 30 kills.",
    "wrongQuestion": "To complete the Achievement \"Desensitized\", you need to complete 300 kills.",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "wrongAnswer": "300"
  },
  {
    "id": "290",
    "questionTemplate": "The Achievement \"Iron Grip\" is completed by getting ______ from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "correctQuestion": "The Achievement \"Iron Grip\" is completed by getting Sigrun's Grips from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Achievement \"Iron Grip\" is completed by getting Elsa's Grips from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sigrun's Grips",
    "wrongAnswer": "Elsa's Grips"
  },
  {
    "id": "291",
    "questionTemplate": "Get Vivi's Loving Gaze from the mysterious treasure chest to complete the Achievement \"______ .",
    "correctQuestion": "Get Vivi's Loving Gaze from the mysterious treasure chest to complete the Achievement \"Making Me Blush\".",
    "wrongQuestion": "Get Vivi's Loving Gaze from the mysterious treasure chest to complete the Achievement \"Shield of Devotion\".",
    "correctAnswer": "Making Me Blush",
    "wrongAnswer": "Shield of Devotion"
  },
  {
    "id": "292",
    "questionTemplate": "The Achievement \"Shield of Devotion\" is completed by getting ______ from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "correctQuestion": "The Achievement \"Shield of Devotion\" is completed by getting Vivi's Loving Protection from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Achievement \"Shield of Devotion\" is completed by getting Mac's Loving Protection from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "correctAnswer": "Vivi's Loving Protection",
    "wrongAnswer": "Mac's Loving Protection"
  },
  {
    "id": "293",
    "questionTemplate": "Get Mac's Vest of Bold Determination from the mysterious treasure chest to complete the Achievement \"______ .",
    "correctQuestion": "Get Mac's Vest of Bold Determination from the mysterious treasure chest to complete the Achievement \"Aye Cap'n!\".",
    "wrongQuestion": "Get Mac's Vest of Bold Determination from the mysterious treasure chest to complete the Achievement \"Yes'm!\".",
    "correctAnswer": "Aye Cap'n!",
    "wrongAnswer": "Yes'm!"
  },
  {
    "id": "294",
    "questionTemplate": "The Achievement \"Utility Belt\" is completed by getting ______ from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "correctQuestion": "The Achievement \"Utility Belt\" is completed by getting Iron Guard's Sturdy Belt from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Achievement \"Utility Belt\" is completed by getting Sigrun's Belt of Protection from the mysterious treasure chest.",
    "correctAnswer": "Iron Guard's Sturdy Belt",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sigrun's Belt of Protection"
  },
  {
    "id": "295",
    "questionTemplate": "The Achievement \"You Need to Cool Off\" is completed by defeating ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Achievement \"You Need to Cool Off\" is completed by defeating <Silent Assassin> Tsubaki.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Achievement \"You Need to Cool Off\" is completed by defeating <Nine-Tailed Vixen> Kotonoha.",
    "correctAnswer": "<Silent Assassin> Tsubaki",
    "wrongAnswer": "<Nine-Tailed Vixen> Kotonoha"
  },
  {
    "id": "296",
    "questionTemplate": "The Achievement \"Animal Control\" is completed by defeating ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Achievement \"Animal Control\" is completed by defeating <Bunnyhop Lord> Beirut.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Achievement \"Animal Control\" is completed by defeating <Local Bully> Bunnyhop Boss.",
    "correctAnswer": "<Bunnyhop Lord> Beirut",
    "wrongAnswer": "<Local Bully> Bunnyhop Boss"
  },
  {
    "id": "297",
    "questionTemplate": "The Achievement \"Floppy Brain's Lobotomy (Party)\" is completed by defeating ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Achievement \"Floppy Brain's Lobotomy (Party)\" is completed by defeating <Deep Sea Jelly> Floppy Brain.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Achievement \"Floppy Brain's Lobotomy (Party)\" is completed by defeating <Sea Slug> Flippity Flop.",
    "correctAnswer": "<Deep Sea Jelly> Floppy Brain",
    "wrongAnswer": "<Sea Slug> Flippity Flop"
  },
  {
    "id": "298",
    "questionTemplate": "Reus believes that true ______ is to try your best to protect those you love.",
    "correctQuestion": "Reus believes that true courage is to try your best to protect those you love.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Reus believes that true justice is to try your best to protect those you love.",
    "correctAnswer": "courage",
    "wrongAnswer": "justice"
  },
  {
    "id": "299",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is not one of Reus's skills.",
    "correctQuestion": "Feline Onslaught is not one of Reus's skills.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Electrical Storm is not one of Reus's skills.",
    "correctAnswer": "Feline Onslaught",
    "wrongAnswer": "Electrical Storm"
  },
  {
    "id": "300",
    "questionTemplate": "Reus has a huge crush on ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Reus has a huge crush on Vivi.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Reus has a huge crush on Endora.",
    "correctAnswer": "Vivi",
    "wrongAnswer": "Endora"
  },
  {
    "id": "301",
    "questionTemplate": "Vivi thinks that ______ is a medicine that nourishes one's heart.",
    "correctQuestion": "Vivi thinks that love is a medicine that nourishes one's heart.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Vivi thinks that fame is a medicine that nourishes one's heart.",
    "correctAnswer": "love",
    "wrongAnswer": "fame"
  },
  {
    "id": "302",
    "questionTemplate": "Vivi's favorite fruit is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Vivi's favorite fruit is apples.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Vivi's favorite fruit is banana.",
    "correctAnswer": "apples",
    "wrongAnswer": "banana"
  },
  {
    "id": "303",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is not one of the the four Eidolons that you can choose when creating a character.",
    "correctQuestion": "Serena is not one of the the four Eidolons that you can choose when creating a character.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Vivi is not one of the the four Eidolons that you can choose when creating a character.",
    "correctAnswer": "Serena",
    "wrongAnswer": "Vivi"
  },
  {
    "id": "304",
    "questionTemplate": "Grimm thinks that the true spirit of ______ is fighting with your friends, sharing the good times and the bad.",
    "correctQuestion": "Grimm thinks that the true spirit of adventure is fighting with your friends, sharing the good times and the bad.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Grimm thinks that the true spirit of battle is fighting with your friends, sharing the good times and the bad.",
    "correctAnswer": "adventure",
    "wrongAnswer": "battle"
  },
  {
    "id": "305",
    "questionTemplate": "Grimm's favorite season is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Grimm's favorite season is summer.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Grimm's favorite season is winter.",
    "correctAnswer": "summer",
    "wrongAnswer": "winter"
  },
  {
    "id": "306",
    "questionTemplate": "Grimm believes that he will one day be able to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Grimm believes that he will one day be able to control the sun and the moon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Grimm believes that he will one day be able to travel through time and space.",
    "correctAnswer": "control the sun and the moon",
    "wrongAnswer": "travel through time and space"
  },
  {
    "id": "307",
    "questionTemplate": "Alessa believes that ______ means no favoritism and no impropriety.",
    "correctQuestion": "Alessa believes that justice means no favoritism and no impropriety.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Alessa believes that honesty means no favoritism and no impropriety.",
    "correctAnswer": "justice",
    "wrongAnswer": "honesty"
  },
  {
    "id": "308",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is not one of the the four Eidolons that you can choose when creating a character.",
    "correctQuestion": "Shaiya is not one of the the four Eidolons that you can choose when creating a character.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Alessa is not one of the the four Eidolons that you can choose when creating a character.",
    "correctAnswer": "Shaiya",
    "wrongAnswer": "Alessa"
  },
  {
    "id": "309",
    "questionTemplate": "Alessa wonders why no one has ever asked her about her wonderful ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Alessa wonders why no one has ever asked her about her wonderful hooves.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Alessa wonders why no one has ever asked her about her wonderful mane.",
    "correctAnswer": "hooves",
    "wrongAnswer": "mane"
  },
  {
    "id": "310",
    "questionTemplate": "Gigas believes that true ______ means not to let your opponents suffer.",
    "correctQuestion": "Gigas believes that true gentleness means not to let your opponents suffer.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Gigas believes that true justice means not to let your opponents suffer.",
    "correctAnswer": "gentleness",
    "wrongAnswer": "justice"
  },
  {
    "id": "311",
    "questionTemplate": "Gigas likes to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Gigas likes to train.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Gigas likes to eat cupcakes.",
    "correctAnswer": "train",
    "wrongAnswer": "eat cupcakes"
  },
  {
    "id": "312",
    "questionTemplate": "The animal Gigas hates most is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The animal Gigas hates most is serpents.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The animal Gigas hates most is spiders.",
    "correctAnswer": "serpents",
    "wrongAnswer": "spiders"
  },
  {
    "id": "313",
    "questionTemplate": "Apollo thinks that ______ are the most important people in life.",
    "correctQuestion": "Apollo thinks that family are the most important people in life.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Apollo thinks that friends are the most important people in life.",
    "correctAnswer": "family",
    "wrongAnswer": "friends"
  },
  {
    "id": "314",
    "questionTemplate": "Of all the instruments, Apollo can play ______ best.",
    "correctQuestion": "Of all the instruments, Apollo can play Harp best.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Of all the instruments, Apollo can play Violin best.",
    "correctAnswer": "Harp",
    "wrongAnswer": "Violin"
  },
  {
    "id": "315",
    "questionTemplate": "Apollo longs for his ______ to forgive him.",
    "correctQuestion": "Apollo longs for his sister to forgive him.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Apollo longs for his brother to forgive him.",
    "correctAnswer": "sister",
    "wrongAnswer": "brother"
  },
  {
    "id": "316",
    "questionTemplate": "Eligos thinks that his greatest weakness ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Eligos thinks that his greatest weakness is non-existent.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Eligos thinks that his greatest weakness is pride.",
    "correctAnswer": "is non-existent",
    "wrongAnswer": "is pride"
  },
  {
    "id": "317",
    "questionTemplate": "Eligos ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Eligos used to have a good friend.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Eligos never had any friends.",
    "correctAnswer": "used to have a good friend",
    "wrongAnswer": "never had any friends"
  },
  {
    "id": "318",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is not one of Eligos' skills.",
    "correctQuestion": "Corrosive Reaper is not one of Eligos' skills.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Moon Slash is not one of Eligos' skills.",
    "correctAnswer": "Corrosive Reaper",
    "wrongAnswer": "Moon Slash"
  },
  {
    "id": "319",
    "questionTemplate": "Sigrun thinks that life is all about ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Sigrun thinks that life is all about battles.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Sigrun thinks that life is all about parties.",
    "correctAnswer": "battles",
    "wrongAnswer": "parties"
  },
  {
    "id": "320",
    "questionTemplate": "Sigrun's ______ is a gift of Gaia.",
    "correctQuestion": "Sigrun's Armor is a gift of Gaia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Sigrun's Sword is a gift of Gaia.",
    "correctAnswer": "Armor",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sword"
  },
  {
    "id": "321",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is not one of Sigrun's skills.",
    "correctQuestion": "As Cold as Ice is not one of Sigrun's skills.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Condensation is not one of Sigrun's skills.",
    "correctAnswer": "As Cold as Ice",
    "wrongAnswer": "Condensation"
  },
  {
    "id": "322",
    "questionTemplate": "Gabrielle thinks that ______ is only a short section of the cycle of life.",
    "correctQuestion": "Gabrielle thinks that death is only a short section of the cycle of life.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Gabrielle thinks that middle-age is only a short section of the cycle of life.",
    "correctAnswer": "death",
    "wrongAnswer": "middle-age"
  },
  {
    "id": "323",
    "questionTemplate": "Gabrielle's dominant hand is her ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Gabrielle's dominant hand is her right hand.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Gabrielle's dominant hand is her left hand.",
    "correctAnswer": "right hand",
    "wrongAnswer": "left hand"
  },
  {
    "id": "324",
    "questionTemplate": "Gabrielle's favorite flowers are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Gabrielle's favorite flowers are lilies.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Gabrielle's favorite flowers are daffodils.",
    "correctAnswer": "lilies",
    "wrongAnswer": "daffodils"
  },
  {
    "id": "325",
    "questionTemplate": "Bel-Chandra's dream is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Bel-Chandra's dream is for all to bow before the peerless beauty of her dance.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Bel-Chandra's dream is to destroy the world with madness.",
    "correctAnswer": "for all to bow before the peerless beauty of her dance",
    "wrongAnswer": "to destroy the world with madness"
  },
  {
    "id": "326",
    "questionTemplate": "Bel-Chandra's third eye can release ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Bel-Chandra's third eye can release Holy Flash.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Bel-Chandra's third eye can release Storm.",
    "correctAnswer": "Holy Flash",
    "wrongAnswer": "Storm"
  },
  {
    "id": "327",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is not one of Bel-Chandra's skills.",
    "correctQuestion": "Furious Dynamo is not one of Bel-Chandra's skills.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Dance of the Conduit is not one of Bel-Chandra's skills.",
    "correctAnswer": "Furious Dynamo",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dance of the Conduit"
  },
  {
    "id": "328",
    "questionTemplate": "Vayu thinks that ______ is the key to getting along with people.",
    "correctQuestion": "Vayu thinks that tolerance is the key to getting along with people.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Vayu thinks that respect is the key to getting along with people.",
    "correctAnswer": "tolerance",
    "wrongAnswer": "respect"
  },
  {
    "id": "329",
    "questionTemplate": "Vayu can't stand it when people %s1",
    "correctQuestion": "Vayu can't stand it when people touch his tender scale.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Vayu can't stand it when people climb on his back.",
    "correctAnswer": "touch his tender scale.",
    "wrongAnswer": "climb on his back."
  },
  {
    "id": "330",
    "questionTemplate": "Vayu used to go to battle together with ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Vayu used to go to battle together with The Dragon Emporor.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Vayu used to go to battle together with his father..",
    "correctAnswer": "The Dragon Emporor",
    "wrongAnswer": "his father."
  },
  {
    "id": "331",
    "questionTemplate": "Yarnaros believes that the greatest power is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Yarnaros believes that the greatest power is speed.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Yarnaros believes that the greatest power is strength.",
    "correctAnswer": "speed",
    "wrongAnswer": "strength"
  },
  {
    "id": "332",
    "questionTemplate": "Yarnaros is not good at ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Yarnaros is not good at riddles.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Yarnaros is not good at meditation.",
    "correctAnswer": "riddles",
    "wrongAnswer": "meditation"
  },
  {
    "id": "333",
    "questionTemplate": "Yarnaros' friends do not include a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Yarnaros' friends do not include a princess.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Yarnaros' friends do not include a powerful king.",
    "correctAnswer": "princess",
    "wrongAnswer": "powerful king"
  },
  {
    "id": "334",
    "questionTemplate": "Quelkulan believes that ______ comes from experience, and experience is distorted by ego.",
    "correctQuestion": "Quelkulan believes that knowledge comes from experience, and experience is distorted by ego.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Quelkulan believes that strength comes from experience, and experience is distorted by ego.",
    "correctAnswer": "knowledge",
    "wrongAnswer": "strength"
  },
  {
    "id": "335",
    "questionTemplate": "Quelkulan is not good at ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Quelkulan is not good at humor.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Quelkulan is not good at healing.",
    "correctAnswer": "humor",
    "wrongAnswer": "healing"
  },
  {
    "id": "336",
    "questionTemplate": "______ was once the sworn enemy of Quelkulan.",
    "correctQuestion": "Gigas was once the sworn enemy of Quelkulan.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Apollo was once the sworn enemy of Quelkulan.",
    "correctAnswer": "Gigas",
    "wrongAnswer": "Apollo"
  },
  {
    "id": "337",
    "questionTemplate": "Zaahir thinks that a friend is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Zaahir thinks that a friend is a person who can share your joys and woes.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Zaahir thinks that a friend is a person who can encourage you.",
    "correctAnswer": "a person who can share your joys and woes",
    "wrongAnswer": "a person who can encourage you"
  },
  {
    "id": "338",
    "questionTemplate": "Zaahir belongs to the race of the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Zaahir belongs to the race of the sprites.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Zaahir belongs to the race of the dragons.",
    "correctAnswer": "sprites",
    "wrongAnswer": "dragons"
  },
  {
    "id": "339",
    "questionTemplate": "Zaahir is known for his ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Zaahir is known for his incredibly high temperature.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Zaahir is known for his very large feet.",
    "correctAnswer": "incredibly high temperature",
    "wrongAnswer": "very large feet"
  },
  {
    "id": "340",
    "questionTemplate": "The animal Kotonoha's likes least is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The animal Kotonoha's likes least is dogs.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The animal Kotonoha's likes least is cats.",
    "correctAnswer": "dogs",
    "wrongAnswer": "cats"
  },
  {
    "id": "341",
    "questionTemplate": "Kotonoha's real form is a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Kotonoha's real form is a golden nine-tailed fox.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Kotonoha's real form is a golden, nine-tailed cat.",
    "correctAnswer": "golden nine-tailed fox",
    "wrongAnswer": "golden, nine-tailed cat"
  },
  {
    "id": "342",
    "questionTemplate": "Kotonoha's favorite food is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Kotonoha's favorite food is inarizushi and fried tofu.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Kotonoha's favorite food is strawberry sundae and chocolate cake.",
    "correctAnswer": "inarizushi and fried tofu",
    "wrongAnswer": "strawberry sundae and chocolate cake"
  },
  {
    "id": "343",
    "questionTemplate": "Tigerius Caesar thinks that ______ is an invisible medal that you put on your coat.",
    "correctQuestion": "Tigerius Caesar thinks that honor is an invisible medal that you put on your coat.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Tigerius Caesar thinks that strength is an invisible medal that you put on your coat.",
    "correctAnswer": "honor",
    "wrongAnswer": "strength"
  },
  {
    "id": "344",
    "questionTemplate": "Tigerius Caesar doesn't enjoy ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Tigerius Caesar doesn't enjoy having his belly rubbed.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Tigerius Caesar doesn't enjoy eating steaks that aren't well-seasoned.",
    "correctAnswer": "having his belly rubbed",
    "wrongAnswer": "eating steaks that aren't well-seasoned"
  },
  {
    "id": "345",
    "questionTemplate": "The only place Tigerius Caesar has failed to conquer is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The only place Tigerius Caesar has failed to conquer is a kingdom in the desert.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The only place Tigerius Caesar has failed to conquer is a kingdom in the mountains.",
    "correctAnswer": "a kingdom in the desert",
    "wrongAnswer": "a kingdom in the mountains"
  },
  {
    "id": "346",
    "questionTemplate": "For Bahadur, ______ protects the rights of the public, even if it means making hard sacrifices.",
    "correctQuestion": "For Bahadur, disciple protects the rights of the public, even if it means making hard sacrifices.",
    "wrongQuestion": "For Bahadur, justice protects the rights of the public, even if it means making hard sacrifices.",
    "correctAnswer": "disciple",
    "wrongAnswer": "justice"
  },
  {
    "id": "347",
    "questionTemplate": "The labyrinth where Bahadur lives in is also his ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The labyrinth where Bahadur lives in is also his underground command post.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The labyrinth where Bahadur lives in is also his banquet hall.",
    "correctAnswer": "underground command post",
    "wrongAnswer": "banquet hall"
  },
  {
    "id": "348",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is not one of Bahadur's skills.",
    "correctQuestion": "Burning Flame Shock is not one of Bahadur's skills.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Heat Wall is not one of Bahadur's skills.",
    "correctAnswer": "Burning Flame Shock",
    "wrongAnswer": "Heat Wall"
  },
  {
    "id": "349",
    "questionTemplate": "Tsubaki is not good at ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Tsubaki is not good at cooking.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Tsubaki is not good at fighting in battle.",
    "correctAnswer": "cooking",
    "wrongAnswer": "fighting in battle"
  },
  {
    "id": "350",
    "questionTemplate": "Tsubaki is not good at using ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Tsubaki is not good at using chopsticks.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Tsubaki is not good at using Shuriken & Kunai.",
    "correctAnswer": "chopsticks",
    "wrongAnswer": "Shuriken & Kunai"
  },
  {
    "id": "351",
    "questionTemplate": "Tsubaki's good friends do not include a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Tsubaki's good friends do not include a Abraxas.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Tsubaki's good friends do not include a Nalani.",
    "correctAnswer": "Abraxas",
    "wrongAnswer": "Nalani"
  },
  {
    "id": "352",
    "questionTemplate": "______ once had a very special relation with Cleopawtra.",
    "correctQuestion": "Tigerius Caesar once had a very special relation with Cleopawtra.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Nazrudin once had a very special relation with Cleopawtra.",
    "correctAnswer": "Tigerius Caesar",
    "wrongAnswer": "Nazrudin"
  },
  {
    "id": "353",
    "questionTemplate": "Cleopawtra wants to know what it is like to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Cleopawtra wants to know what it is like to conquer a kingdom.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Cleopawtra wants to know what it is like to conquer her fear of flying.",
    "correctAnswer": "conquer a kingdom",
    "wrongAnswer": "conquer her fear of flying"
  },
  {
    "id": "354",
    "questionTemplate": "Cleopatra's best feature is her ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Cleopatra's best feature is her eyes.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Cleopatra's best feature is her fur.",
    "correctAnswer": "eyes",
    "wrongAnswer": "fur"
  },
  {
    "id": "355",
    "questionTemplate": "Serena's weapon is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Serena's weapon is a book.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Serena's weapon is a blade.",
    "correctAnswer": "a book",
    "wrongAnswer": "a blade"
  },
  {
    "id": "356",
    "questionTemplate": "______ are Serena' favorite animal.",
    "correctQuestion": "rabbits are Serena' favorite animal.",
    "wrongQuestion": "penguins are Serena' favorite animal.",
    "correctAnswer": "rabbits",
    "wrongAnswer": "penguins"
  },
  {
    "id": "357",
    "questionTemplate": "Serena doesn't want to talk to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Serena doesn't want to talk to Apollo.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Serena doesn't want to talk to Gigas.",
    "correctAnswer": "Apollo",
    "wrongAnswer": "Gigas"
  },
  {
    "id": "358",
    "questionTemplate": "Endora's secret pleasure is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Endora's secret pleasure is sneaking into people's dreams.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Endora's secret pleasure is playing with kittens.",
    "correctAnswer": "sneaking into people's dreams",
    "wrongAnswer": "playing with kittens"
  },
  {
    "id": "359",
    "questionTemplate": "Endora has a crush on ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Endora has a crush on Reus.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Endora has a crush on Eligos.",
    "correctAnswer": "Reus",
    "wrongAnswer": "Eligos"
  },
  {
    "id": "360",
    "questionTemplate": "______ and Endora's weapons come from the same place.",
    "correctQuestion": "Vivi and Endora's weapons come from the same place.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Serena and Endora's weapons come from the same place.",
    "correctAnswer": "Vivi",
    "wrongAnswer": "Serena"
  },
  {
    "id": "361",
    "questionTemplate": "Winged Butterfly Maya is ______ than her sister Mia.",
    "correctQuestion": "Winged Butterfly Maya is older than her sister Mia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Winged Butterfly Maya is younger than her sister Mia.",
    "correctAnswer": "older",
    "wrongAnswer": "younger"
  },
  {
    "id": "362",
    "questionTemplate": "Winged Butterfly Mia is ______ than her sister Maya.",
    "correctQuestion": "Winged Butterfly Mia is younger than her sister Maya.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Winged Butterfly Mia is older than her sister Maya.",
    "correctAnswer": "younger",
    "wrongAnswer": "older"
  },
  {
    "id": "363",
    "questionTemplate": "Envoy of Gaia Mia's title is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Envoy of Gaia Mia's title is Right-Wing Butterfly.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Envoy of Gaia Mia's title is Left-Wing Butterfly.",
    "correctAnswer": "Right-Wing Butterfly",
    "wrongAnswer": "Left-Wing Butterfly"
  },
  {
    "id": "364",
    "questionTemplate": "Envoy of Gaia Maya's title is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Envoy of Gaia Maya's title is Left-Wing Butterfly.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Envoy of Gaia Maya's title is Right-Wing Butterfly.",
    "correctAnswer": "Left-Wing Butterfly",
    "wrongAnswer": "Right-Wing Butterfly"
  },
  {
    "id": "365",
    "questionTemplate": "Beebis was not raised by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Beebis was not raised by Flower.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Beebis was not raised by Elena.",
    "correctAnswer": "Flower",
    "wrongAnswer": "Elena"
  },
  {
    "id": "366",
    "questionTemplate": "Elena and Flower of Port Skandia are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Elena and Flower of Port Skandia are a witch and her assistant.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Elena and Flower of Port Skandia are siblings.",
    "correctAnswer": "a witch and her assistant",
    "wrongAnswer": "siblings"
  },
  {
    "id": "367",
    "questionTemplate": "______ was working on the translation of the runestones in Port Skandia.",
    "correctQuestion": "Miles was working on the translation of the runestones in Port Skandia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Elena was working on the translation of the runestones in Port Skandia.",
    "correctAnswer": "Miles",
    "wrongAnswer": "Elena"
  },
  {
    "id": "368",
    "questionTemplate": "When the Envoy of Gaia fights against Brian in the Hidden Cave, his Eidolon is a ______",
    "correctQuestion": "When the Envoy of Gaia fights against Brian in the Hidden Cave, his Eidolon is a bloodthirsty panther.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When the Envoy of Gaia fights against Brian in the Hidden Cave, his Eidolon is a bloodthirsty wolf.",
    "correctAnswer": "bloodthirsty panther",
    "wrongAnswer": "bloodthirsty wolf"
  },
  {
    "id": "369",
    "questionTemplate": "The best fighter in Lunarin in Crescent Hill is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The best fighter in Lunarin in Crescent Hill is Foreman Potter.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The best fighter in Lunarin in Crescent Hill is Young Man Halton.",
    "correctAnswer": "Foreman Potter",
    "wrongAnswer": "Young Man Halton"
  },
  {
    "id": "370",
    "questionTemplate": "In Crescent Hill, ______ brings players into Navea.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Crescent Hill, Anya brings players into Navea.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Crescent Hill, Victoria brings players into Navea.",
    "correctAnswer": "Anya",
    "wrongAnswer": "Victoria"
  },
  {
    "id": "371",
    "questionTemplate": "Assistant Craftsman Paolo, located outside the Alabastren Temple, comes from ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Assistant Craftsman Paolo, located outside the Alabastren Temple, comes from Cactakara Forest.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Assistant Craftsman Paolo, located outside the Alabastren Temple, comes from Crescent Hill.",
    "correctAnswer": "Cactakara Forest",
    "wrongAnswer": "Crescent Hill"
  },
  {
    "id": "372",
    "questionTemplate": "When you first arrived in Crescent Hill, ______ wasn't too fond of outsiders.",
    "correctQuestion": "When you first arrived in Crescent Hill, Lunarin Chief Omar wasn't too fond of outsiders.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When you first arrived in Crescent Hill, Old Craftsman Anthony wasn't too fond of outsiders.",
    "correctAnswer": "Lunarin Chief Omar",
    "wrongAnswer": "Old Craftsman Anthony"
  },
  {
    "id": "373",
    "questionTemplate": "In Lunarin in Crescent Hill, Chief Omar and Young Man Halton are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Lunarin in Crescent Hill, Chief Omar and Young Man Halton are grandfather and grandson.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Lunarin in Crescent Hill, Chief Omar and Young Man Halton are father and son.",
    "correctAnswer": "grandfather and grandson",
    "wrongAnswer": "father and son"
  },
  {
    "id": "374",
    "questionTemplate": "In Navea, the ladies who do business in Dome Square are dying to meet ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Navea, the ladies who do business in Dome Square are dying to meet Guard Officer Gus.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Navea, the ladies who do business in Dome Square are dying to meet Templar Commander Andre.",
    "correctAnswer": "Guard Officer Gus",
    "wrongAnswer": "Templar Commander Andre"
  },
  {
    "id": "375",
    "questionTemplate": "Scholar Miles, who was killed in the Demarech Mines, is a great authority on ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Scholar Miles, who was killed in the Demarech Mines, is a great authority on Ancient Languages.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Scholar Miles, who was killed in the Demarech Mines, is a great authority on Dimensional Fissures.",
    "correctAnswer": "Ancient Languages",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dimensional Fissures"
  },
  {
    "id": "376",
    "questionTemplate": "After defeating the Oracle Gnomes, King Leo declares that ______ will be the new leader of the Ventos Tribe.",
    "correctQuestion": "After defeating the Oracle Gnomes, King Leo declares that Second Prince Para Ryan will be the new leader of the Ventos Tribe.",
    "wrongQuestion": "After defeating the Oracle Gnomes, King Leo declares that Eldest Prince Palo Ryan will be the new leader of the Ventos Tribe.",
    "correctAnswer": "Second Prince Para Ryan",
    "wrongAnswer": "Eldest Prince Palo Ryan"
  },
  {
    "id": "377",
    "questionTemplate": "Eldest Prince Palo Ryan gets poisoned by the ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Eldest Prince Palo Ryan gets poisoned by the Gnome's Potion.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Eldest Prince Palo Ryan gets poisoned by the Avian's Potion.",
    "correctAnswer": "Gnome's Potion",
    "wrongAnswer": "Avian's Potion"
  },
  {
    "id": "378",
    "questionTemplate": "Imperial Bodyguard Shalen of Ventos Prairie once served ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Imperial Bodyguard Shalen of Ventos Prairie once served Third Prince Odum Ryan.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Imperial Bodyguard Shalen of Ventos Prairie once served Rebel General Micha.",
    "correctAnswer": "Third Prince Odum Ryan",
    "wrongAnswer": "Rebel General Micha"
  },
  {
    "id": "379",
    "questionTemplate": "The relationship between Old Man Harvey of Demarech Mines and Knight Blacksmith Analisa is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The relationship between Old Man Harvey of Demarech Mines and Knight Blacksmith Analisa is master and assistant.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The relationship between Old Man Harvey of Demarech Mines and Knight Blacksmith Analisa is father and daughter.",
    "correctAnswer": "master and assistant",
    "wrongAnswer": "father and daughter"
  },
  {
    "id": "380",
    "questionTemplate": "In Demarech Mines, ______ is badly injured while saving his father.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, Young Man Bobby is badly injured while saving his father.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, Merchant Luther is badly injured while saving his father.",
    "correctAnswer": "Young Man Bobby",
    "wrongAnswer": "Merchant Luther"
  },
  {
    "id": "381",
    "questionTemplate": "In Fulcheth Forest of Oblitus Wood, the children of Krok Village ______ Church Guard Zachary.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Fulcheth Forest of Oblitus Wood, the children of Krok Village like Church Guard Zachary.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Fulcheth Forest of Oblitus Wood, the children of Krok Village are you afraid of Church Guard Zachary.",
    "correctAnswer": "like",
    "wrongAnswer": "are you afraid of"
  },
  {
    "id": "382",
    "questionTemplate": "Analisa's apprentice, Byron, is most afraid of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Analisa's apprentice, Byron, is most afraid of riding on animals.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Analisa's apprentice, Byron, is most afraid of practicing forging.",
    "correctAnswer": "riding on animals",
    "wrongAnswer": "practicing forging"
  },
  {
    "id": "383",
    "questionTemplate": "Templar Commander Andre usually uses ______ as his weapon.",
    "correctQuestion": "Templar Commander Andre usually uses Sword and Shield as his weapon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Templar Commander Andre usually uses Dual Blades as his weapon.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sword and Shield",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dual Blades"
  },
  {
    "id": "384",
    "questionTemplate": "Near Castle Church stands Horace, a scholar of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Near Castle Church stands Horace, a scholar of Zombies.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Near Castle Church stands Horace, a scholar of Ancient Scripts.",
    "correctAnswer": "Zombies",
    "wrongAnswer": "Ancient Scripts"
  },
  {
    "id": "385",
    "questionTemplate": "In Navea, Banker Thorne's necklace is stolen by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Navea, Banker Thorne's necklace is stolen by Fleet Footed Adie.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Navea, Banker Thorne's necklace is stolen by Short Footed Adie.",
    "correctAnswer": "Fleet Footed Adie",
    "wrongAnswer": "Short Footed Adie"
  },
  {
    "id": "386",
    "questionTemplate": "Lucas, who was killed in Candeo Marsh, lived in ______ with his wife.",
    "correctQuestion": "Lucas, who was killed in Candeo Marsh, lived in Helonia with his wife.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Lucas, who was killed in Candeo Marsh, lived in Candetonn with his wife.",
    "correctAnswer": "Helonia",
    "wrongAnswer": "Candetonn"
  },
  {
    "id": "387",
    "questionTemplate": "The Templar who won the battle against the Corpser Bandits is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Templar who won the battle against the Corpser Bandits is Alex.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Templar who won the battle against the Corpser Bandits is Anya.",
    "correctAnswer": "Alex",
    "wrongAnswer": "Anya"
  },
  {
    "id": "388",
    "questionTemplate": "The Tafay Chief's name is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Tafay Chief's name is Tobin.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Tafay Chief's name is Dolan.",
    "correctAnswer": "Tobin",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dolan"
  },
  {
    "id": "389",
    "questionTemplate": "The champion of the last Robot Competition was ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The champion of the last Robot Competition was Montero the Mechanic.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The champion of the last Robot Competition was Augustus.",
    "correctAnswer": "Montero the Mechanic",
    "wrongAnswer": "Augustus"
  },
  {
    "id": "390",
    "questionTemplate": "Henry and Mark in Fernscall Woods of Candeo Marsh were once commanded by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Henry and Mark in Fernscall Woods of Candeo Marsh were once commanded by Alex.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Henry and Mark in Fernscall Woods of Candeo Marsh were once commanded by Anya.",
    "correctAnswer": "Alex",
    "wrongAnswer": "Anya"
  },
  {
    "id": "391",
    "questionTemplate": "The brothers Isaac and Braeden of Helonia are professional ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The brothers Isaac and Braeden of Helonia are professional Fisherman.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The brothers Isaac and Braeden of Helonia are professional Hunters.",
    "correctAnswer": "Fisherman",
    "wrongAnswer": "Hunters"
  },
  {
    "id": "392",
    "questionTemplate": "In Candeo Core, the Shadow Knight tries to convince Templar ______ to switch sides.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Candeo Core, the Shadow Knight tries to convince Templar Alex to switch sides.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Candeo Core, the Shadow Knight tries to convince Templar Andre to switch sides.",
    "correctAnswer": "Alex",
    "wrongAnswer": "Andre"
  },
  {
    "id": "393",
    "questionTemplate": "Jill, the little girl who appears both in Navea and Oblitus Wood, is the daughter of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Jill, the little girl who appears both in Navea and Oblitus Wood, is the daughter of Analisa.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Jill, the little girl who appears both in Navea and Oblitus Wood, is the daughter of Victoria.",
    "correctAnswer": "Analisa",
    "wrongAnswer": "Victoria"
  },
  {
    "id": "394",
    "questionTemplate": "The dish that Bella makes to bribe Achemist Perry is called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The dish that Bella makes to bribe Achemist Perry is called Spicy Apple Escargot.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The dish that Bella makes to bribe Achemist Perry is called Helonian Fruit Jelly.",
    "correctAnswer": "Spicy Apple Escargot",
    "wrongAnswer": "Helonian Fruit Jelly"
  },
  {
    "id": "395",
    "questionTemplate": "Braeden, the younger of the two fisherman in Helonia, has ______ hair.",
    "correctQuestion": "Braeden, the younger of the two fisherman in Helonia, has Blond hair.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Braeden, the younger of the two fisherman in Helonia, has Brown hair.",
    "correctAnswer": "Blond",
    "wrongAnswer": "Brown"
  },
  {
    "id": "396",
    "questionTemplate": "Isaac, the older of the two fisherman in Helonia, has ______ hair.",
    "correctQuestion": "Isaac, the older of the two fisherman in Helonia, has Brown hair.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Isaac, the older of the two fisherman in Helonia, has Blond hair.",
    "correctAnswer": "Brown",
    "wrongAnswer": "Blond"
  },
  {
    "id": "397",
    "questionTemplate": "In Navea, Barry is responsible for ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Navea, Barry is responsible for guarding Sky Tower.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Navea, Barry is responsible for handling Guild Affairs.",
    "correctAnswer": "guarding Sky Tower",
    "wrongAnswer": "handling Guild Affairs"
  },
  {
    "id": "398",
    "questionTemplate": "In the church audience chamber in Navea, the name of the Grand Bishop is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the church audience chamber in Navea, the name of the Grand Bishop is Belenus.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the church audience chamber in Navea, the name of the Grand Bishop is Lucius.",
    "correctAnswer": "Belenus",
    "wrongAnswer": "Lucius"
  },
  {
    "id": "399",
    "questionTemplate": "Odum Ryan and Blacksmith Analisa met for the first time at ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Odum Ryan and Blacksmith Analisa met for the first time at Oblitus Wood.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Odum Ryan and Blacksmith Analisa met for the first time at Navea.",
    "correctAnswer": "Oblitus Wood",
    "wrongAnswer": "Navea"
  },
  {
    "id": "400",
    "questionTemplate": "The Templar with the long, shaggy hair is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Templar with the long, shaggy hair is Alex.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Templar with the long, shaggy hair is Andre.",
    "correctAnswer": "Alex",
    "wrongAnswer": "Andre"
  },
  {
    "id": "401",
    "questionTemplate": "When the Dragon appeared in Helonia Coast, the first Eidolon to meet it was ______",
    "correctQuestion": "When the Dragon appeared in Helonia Coast, the first Eidolon to meet it was Apollo.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When the Dragon appeared in Helonia Coast, the first Eidolon to meet it was Sigrun.",
    "correctAnswer": "Apollo",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sigrun"
  },
  {
    "id": "402",
    "questionTemplate": "In Miner's Steppe, ______ attacks Investigation Team Vice Leader Floyd.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Miner's Steppe, Assistant Maggie attacks Investigation Team Vice Leader Floyd.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Miner's Steppe, Marauder Captain Qulun attacks Investigation Team Vice Leader Floyd.",
    "correctAnswer": "Assistant Maggie",
    "wrongAnswer": "Marauder Captain Qulun"
  },
  {
    "id": "403",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Star Sand Desert, the local boy Haas wants to help because ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Star Sand Desert, the local boy Haas wants to help because he wants to earn some extra money.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Star Sand Desert, the local boy Haas wants to help because he wants to pay a debt of gratitude.",
    "correctAnswer": "he wants to earn some extra money",
    "wrongAnswer": "he wants to pay a debt of gratitude"
  },
  {
    "id": "404",
    "questionTemplate": "The dragon Wrenna was once sealed by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The dragon Wrenna was once sealed by <Immortal Demon> Talamund.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The dragon Wrenna was once sealed by <Desert Guide> Akara.",
    "correctAnswer": "<Immortal Demon> Talamund",
    "wrongAnswer": "<Desert Guide> Akara"
  },
  {
    "id": "405",
    "questionTemplate": "In Candetonn, Grandpa Will declares that he saw ______ with his own eyes.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Candetonn, Grandpa Will declares that he saw Vampires with his own eyes.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Candetonn, Grandpa Will declares that he saw Bats with his own eyes.",
    "correctAnswer": "Vampires",
    "wrongAnswer": "Bats"
  },
  {
    "id": "406",
    "questionTemplate": "In Hunters' Mountain Village, Village Chief Dallan and Chef Kara are ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Hunters' Mountain Village, Village Chief Dallan and Chef Kara are mother and son.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Hunters' Mountain Village, Village Chief Dallan and Chef Kara are master and servant.",
    "correctAnswer": "mother and son",
    "wrongAnswer": "master and servant"
  },
  {
    "id": "407",
    "questionTemplate": "Chef Kara of Hunters' Mountain Village was once a ______ when he was young.",
    "correctQuestion": "Chef Kara of Hunters' Mountain Village was once a hunter when he was young.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Chef Kara of Hunters' Mountain Village was once a doctor when he was young.",
    "correctAnswer": "hunter",
    "wrongAnswer": "doctor"
  },
  {
    "id": "408",
    "questionTemplate": "When you joined the Robot Competition in Cactakara Forest, Montero's robot was named ______",
    "correctQuestion": "When you joined the Robot Competition in Cactakara Forest, Montero's robot was named Robot Montebrown Mk.V.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When you joined the Robot Competition in Cactakara Forest, Montero's robot was named Robot Prototype Pierre.",
    "correctAnswer": "Robot Montebrown Mk.V",
    "wrongAnswer": "Robot Prototype Pierre"
  },
  {
    "id": "409",
    "questionTemplate": "Garrison Captain Kane at Port Skandia hopes that you and Brian ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Garrison Captain Kane at Port Skandia hopes that you and Brian kill each other.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Garrison Captain Kane at Port Skandia hopes that you and Brian become good friends.",
    "correctAnswer": "kill each other",
    "wrongAnswer": "become good friends"
  },
  {
    "id": "410",
    "questionTemplate": "In Navea, ______ accompanied you on the Ostrich Ride.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Navea, Blacksmith Apprentice Byron accompanied you on the Ostrich Ride.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Navea, Merchant Luther accompanied you on the Ostrich Ride.",
    "correctAnswer": "Blacksmith Apprentice Byron",
    "wrongAnswer": "Merchant Luther"
  },
  {
    "id": "411",
    "questionTemplate": "In Navea, ______ is in charge of refining.",
    "correctQuestion": "In Navea, Analisa is in charge of refining.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Navea, Jill is in charge of refining.",
    "correctAnswer": "Analisa",
    "wrongAnswer": "Jill"
  },
  {
    "id": "412",
    "questionTemplate": "Weapons Refining is available for level ______ and above.",
    "correctQuestion": "Weapons Refining is available for level 40 and above.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Weapons Refining is available for level 30 and above.",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "wrongAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "id": "413",
    "questionTemplate": "The Attack Bonus for refined weapons can be as high as ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Attack Bonus for refined weapons can be as high as 130.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Attack Bonus for refined weapons can be as high as 140.",
    "correctAnswer": "130",
    "wrongAnswer": "140"
  },
  {
    "id": "414",
    "questionTemplate": "You can refine a Lightning Guardsman's Sword and Shield to create ______ Defender's Sword and Shield.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can refine a Lightning Guardsman's Sword and Shield to create Holy Flash Defender's Sword and Shield.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can refine a Lightning Guardsman's Sword and Shield to create Random Defender's Sword and Shield.",
    "correctAnswer": "Holy Flash",
    "wrongAnswer": "Random"
  },
  {
    "id": "415",
    "questionTemplate": "Refining Cores ______ be added to a green quality base item.",
    "correctQuestion": "Refining Cores can be added to a green quality base item.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Refining Cores cannot be added to a green quality base item.",
    "correctAnswer": "can",
    "wrongAnswer": "cannot"
  },
  {
    "id": "416",
    "questionTemplate": "The highest Expertise Rating for a recipe is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The highest Expertise Rating for a recipe is A.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The highest Expertise Rating for a recipe is S.",
    "correctAnswer": "A",
    "wrongAnswer": "S"
  },
  {
    "id": "417",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Demarech Mines, ______  will help you with Precision Forging.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Demarech Mines, Harvey  will help you with Precision Forging.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Demarech Mines, Denton  will help you with Precision Forging.",
    "correctAnswer": "Harvey",
    "wrongAnswer": "Denton"
  },
  {
    "id": "418",
    "questionTemplate": "You can obtain ______ through the Refining System.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can obtain Adjudicator's Sword and Shield through the Refining System.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can obtain Zaahir's Unyielding Sword and Shield through the Refining System.",
    "correctAnswer": "Adjudicator's Sword and Shield",
    "wrongAnswer": "Zaahir's Unyielding Sword and Shield"
  },
  {
    "id": "419",
    "questionTemplate": "Amaranth ______ one of the materials needed to make a Refining Core.",
    "correctQuestion": "Amaranth is not one of the materials needed to make a Refining Core.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Amaranth is one of the materials needed to make a Refining Core.",
    "correctAnswer": "is not",
    "wrongAnswer": "is"
  },
  {
    "id": "420",
    "questionTemplate": "When refining weapons, the attack bonus of your green quality weapon ______ influence the attack bonus of the refined orange quality weapon.",
    "correctQuestion": "When refining weapons, the attack bonus of your green quality weapon will influence the attack bonus of the refined orange quality weapon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When refining weapons, the attack bonus of your green quality weapon will not influence the attack bonus of the refined orange quality weapon.",
    "correctAnswer": "will",
    "wrongAnswer": "will not"
  },
  {
    "id": "421",
    "questionTemplate": "You ______ forge Eidolon Accessories after buying recipes.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can forge Eidolon Accessories after buying recipes.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You cannot forge Eidolon Accessories after buying recipes.",
    "correctAnswer": "can",
    "wrongAnswer": "cannot"
  },
  {
    "id": "422",
    "questionTemplate": "You ______ create Gold Quality Cuisine by Refining it.",
    "correctQuestion": "You cannot create Gold Quality Cuisine by Refining it.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can create Gold Quality Cuisine by Refining it.",
    "correctAnswer": "cannot",
    "wrongAnswer": "can"
  },
  {
    "id": "423",
    "questionTemplate": "When Forging, it ______ possible for the attempt to fail and to lose all materials.",
    "correctQuestion": "When Forging, it is not possible for the attempt to fail and to lose all materials.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When Forging, it is possible for the attempt to fail and to lose all materials.",
    "correctAnswer": "is not",
    "wrongAnswer": "is"
  },
  {
    "id": "424",
    "questionTemplate": "You ______ create powerful Fishing Equipment through Fusion.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can create powerful Fishing Equipment through Fusion.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You cannot create powerful Fishing Equipment through Fusion.",
    "correctAnswer": "can",
    "wrongAnswer": "cannot"
  },
  {
    "id": "425",
    "questionTemplate": "The bonus stats of items created by Forging ______  when you make them.",
    "correctQuestion": "The bonus stats of items created by Forging has nothing to do with  when you make them.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The bonus stats of items created by Forging is closely related to  when you make them.",
    "correctAnswer": "has nothing to do with",
    "wrongAnswer": "is closely related to"
  },
  {
    "id": "426",
    "questionTemplate": "The Secret Stones that can increase the CRIT Rate of skills are called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the CRIT Rate of skills are called Sunrise Secret Stones.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the CRIT Rate of skills are called Crimson Secret Stone.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sunrise Secret Stones",
    "wrongAnswer": "Crimson Secret Stone"
  },
  {
    "id": "427",
    "questionTemplate": "The Secret Stones that can increase the CRIT DMG of skills are called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the CRIT DMG of skills are called Golden Secret Stones.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the CRIT DMG of skills are called Sunset Secret Stones.",
    "correctAnswer": "Golden Secret Stones",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sunset Secret Stones"
  },
  {
    "id": "428",
    "questionTemplate": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Effect Duration of skills are called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Effect Duration of skills are called Emerald Secret Stone.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Effect Duration of skills are called Azure Secret Stone.",
    "correctAnswer": "Emerald Secret Stone",
    "wrongAnswer": "Azure Secret Stone"
  },
  {
    "id": "429",
    "questionTemplate": "The Secret Stones that can decrease the Cooldown of skills are called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can decrease the Cooldown of skills are called Azure Secret Stone.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can decrease the Cooldown of skills are called Golden Secret Stones.",
    "correctAnswer": "Azure Secret Stone",
    "wrongAnswer": "Golden Secret Stones"
  },
  {
    "id": "430",
    "questionTemplate": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Radius of skills are called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Radius of skills are called Indigo Secret Stones.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Radius of skills are called Sunset Secret Stones.",
    "correctAnswer": "Indigo Secret Stones",
    "wrongAnswer": "Sunset Secret Stones"
  },
  {
    "id": "431",
    "questionTemplate": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Range of skills are called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Range of skills are called Sunset Secret Stones.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Secret Stones that can increase the Range of skills are called Golden Secret Stones.",
    "correctAnswer": "Sunset Secret Stones",
    "wrongAnswer": "Golden Secret Stones"
  },
  {
    "id": "432",
    "questionTemplate": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in weapons is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in weapons is round.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in weapons is triangle.",
    "correctAnswer": "round",
    "wrongAnswer": "triangle"
  },
  {
    "id": "433",
    "questionTemplate": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in helmets is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in helmets is diamond.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in helmets is octagon.",
    "correctAnswer": "diamond",
    "wrongAnswer": "octagon"
  },
  {
    "id": "434",
    "questionTemplate": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in armor is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in armor is hexagon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in armor is round.",
    "correctAnswer": "hexagon",
    "wrongAnswer": "round"
  },
  {
    "id": "435",
    "questionTemplate": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in gloves is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in gloves is triangle.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in gloves is hexagon.",
    "correctAnswer": "triangle",
    "wrongAnswer": "hexagon"
  },
  {
    "id": "436",
    "questionTemplate": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in boots is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in boots is teardrop.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in boots is square.",
    "correctAnswer": "teardrop",
    "wrongAnswer": "square"
  },
  {
    "id": "437",
    "questionTemplate": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in belts is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in belts is square.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The shape of Secret Stones which can be inlaid in belts is teardrop.",
    "correctAnswer": "square",
    "wrongAnswer": "teardrop"
  },
  {
    "id": "438",
    "questionTemplate": "The books left by the ancient heroes are called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The books left by the ancient heroes are called Mastery Books.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The books left by the ancient heroes are called Bibles.",
    "correctAnswer": "Mastery Books",
    "wrongAnswer": "Bibles"
  },
  {
    "id": "439",
    "questionTemplate": "To Fortify an item, you need a large number of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "To Fortify an item, you need a large number of Fragments.",
    "wrongQuestion": "To Fortify an item, you need a large number of Scrolls.",
    "correctAnswer": "Fragments",
    "wrongAnswer": "Scrolls"
  },
  {
    "id": "440",
    "questionTemplate": "If the attempt to Fortify fails, ______ is increased.",
    "correctQuestion": "If the attempt to Fortify fails, Potential Points is increased.",
    "wrongQuestion": "If the attempt to Fortify fails, Power Points is increased.",
    "correctAnswer": "Potential Points",
    "wrongAnswer": "Power Points"
  },
  {
    "id": "441",
    "questionTemplate": "When an item's potential reaches 100, it's fortification level will automatically ______",
    "correctQuestion": "When an item's potential reaches 100, it's fortification level will automatically increase by 1.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When an item's potential reaches 100, it's fortification level will automatically decrease by 1.",
    "correctAnswer": "increase by 1",
    "wrongAnswer": "decrease by 1"
  },
  {
    "id": "442",
    "questionTemplate": "When you start your journey on the Envoy's Path, you must first choose your ______",
    "correctQuestion": "When you start your journey on the Envoy's Path, you must first choose your Class.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When you start your journey on the Envoy's Path, you must first choose your Secondary Weapon.",
    "correctAnswer": "Class",
    "wrongAnswer": "Secondary Weapon"
  },
  {
    "id": "443",
    "questionTemplate": "By greeting your friends online, you can earn ______",
    "correctQuestion": "By greeting your friends online, you can earn Loyalty points.",
    "wrongQuestion": "By greeting your friends online, you can earn friendship points.",
    "correctAnswer": "Loyalty points",
    "wrongAnswer": "friendship points"
  },
  {
    "id": "444",
    "questionTemplate": "The Rankings are updated everyday at ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Rankings are updated everyday at 5 A.M..",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Rankings are updated everyday at 6 A.M..",
    "correctAnswer": "5 A.M.",
    "wrongAnswer": "6 A.M."
  },
  {
    "id": "445",
    "questionTemplate": "You can earn ______ by completing quests.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can earn Tokens by completing quests.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can earn Explorer Coins by completing quests.",
    "correctAnswer": "Tokens",
    "wrongAnswer": "Explorer Coins"
  },
  {
    "id": "446",
    "questionTemplate": "You can earn ______ by competing in the Arena.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can earn War Coins by competing in the Arena.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can earn Battle Coins by competing in the Arena.",
    "correctAnswer": "War Coins",
    "wrongAnswer": "Battle Coins"
  },
  {
    "id": "447",
    "questionTemplate": "Players can only set up a stall in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Players can only set up a stall in the Stall Area.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Players can only set up a stall in Candeo Marsh.",
    "correctAnswer": "the Stall Area",
    "wrongAnswer": "Candeo Marsh"
  },
  {
    "id": "448",
    "questionTemplate": "You can equip ______ Trophy of the same kind at once.",
    "correctQuestion": "You can equip only one Trophy of the same kind at once.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can equip more than one Trophy of the same kind at once.",
    "correctAnswer": "only one",
    "wrongAnswer": "more than one"
  },
  {
    "id": "449",
    "questionTemplate": "Talking with Eidolons can increase their ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Talking with Eidolons can increase their Energy.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Talking with Eidolons can increase their Magic.",
    "correctAnswer": "Energy",
    "wrongAnswer": "Magic"
  },
  {
    "id": "450",
    "questionTemplate": "Using potions automatically in battle is called ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Using potions automatically in battle is called Auto-Potion.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Using potions automatically in battle is called Auto-Drink.",
    "correctAnswer": "Auto-Potion",
    "wrongAnswer": "Auto-Drink"
  },
  {
    "id": "451",
    "questionTemplate": "You must reach Level ______ to found your own guild.",
    "correctQuestion": "You must reach Level 20 to found your own guild.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You must reach Level 25 to found your own guild.",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "wrongAnswer": "25"
  },
  {
    "id": "452",
    "questionTemplate": "You can choose a Secondary Class after reaching Level ______",
    "correctQuestion": "You can choose a Secondary Class after reaching Level 40.",
    "wrongQuestion": "You can choose a Secondary Class after reaching Level 45.",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "wrongAnswer": "45"
  },
  {
    "id": "453",
    "questionTemplate": "Eidolon Evolution will dramatically increase their ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Eidolon Evolution will dramatically increase their stats.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Eidolon Evolution will dramatically increase their magic.",
    "correctAnswer": "stats",
    "wrongAnswer": "magic"
  },
  {
    "id": "454",
    "questionTemplate": "From Level ______ on, players can spend their Envoy's Path Points.",
    "correctQuestion": "From Level 3 on, players can spend their Envoy's Path Points.",
    "wrongQuestion": "From Level 5 on, players can spend their Envoy's Path Points.",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "455",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Eclipse Rabbit Cave,\" ______ stole the Moonlight Rice Cake.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Eclipse Rabbit Cave,\" Eclipse Rabbit Tribe stole the Moonlight Rice Cake.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Eclipse Rabbit Cave,\" Moonlight Rabbit Tribe stole the Moonlight Rice Cake.",
    "correctAnswer": "Eclipse Rabbit Tribe",
    "wrongAnswer": "Moonlight Rabbit Tribe"
  },
  {
    "id": "456",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is the Elder of the Moonlight Rabbit Tribe in Crescent Hill.",
    "correctQuestion": "Immanuel is the Elder of the Moonlight Rabbit Tribe in Crescent Hill.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Layla is the Elder of the Moonlight Rabbit Tribe in Crescent Hill.",
    "correctAnswer": "Immanuel",
    "wrongAnswer": "Layla"
  },
  {
    "id": "457",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Lightless Firework Village,\" ______ attacks the village.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Lightless Firework Village,\" Daq attacks the village.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Lightless Firework Village,\" Erwin attacks the village.",
    "correctAnswer": "Daq",
    "wrongAnswer": "Erwin"
  },
  {
    "id": "458",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Lightless Firework Village,\" ______ is the Guardian Sprite.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Lightless Firework Village,\" Floret is the Guardian Sprite.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Lightless Firework Village,\" Daq is the Guardian Sprite.",
    "correctAnswer": "Floret",
    "wrongAnswer": "Daq"
  },
  {
    "id": "459",
    "questionTemplate": "In the \"Turkey Time\" quest in Coast of Helionia, the turkey is fully cooked after ______ times on the grill.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the \"Turkey Time\" quest in Coast of Helionia, the turkey is fully cooked after 8 times on the grill.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the \"Turkey Time\" quest in Coast of Helionia, the turkey is fully cooked after 9 times on the grill.",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "wrongAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "460",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Machinery Ruins,\" the engine overheats, causing the device to crash after ______ flights.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Machinery Ruins,\" the engine overheats, causing the device to crash after 3 flights.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Machinery Ruins,\" the engine overheats, causing the device to crash after 2 flights.",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "461",
    "questionTemplate": "Astra sends the chocolate from ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Astra sends the chocolate from Helonia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Astra sends the chocolate from Skandia.",
    "correctAnswer": "Helonia",
    "wrongAnswer": "Skandia"
  },
  {
    "id": "462",
    "questionTemplate": "When Astra asks the Envoy of Gaia to dispatch the Secret Valentine's Chocolate, the recipient's name is written %s1",
    "correctQuestion": "When Astra asks the Envoy of Gaia to dispatch the Secret Valentine's Chocolate, the recipient's name is written on a card on the packaging.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When Astra asks the Envoy of Gaia to dispatch the Secret Valentine's Chocolate, the recipient's name is written on the chocolate wrapping paper.",
    "correctAnswer": "on a card on the packaging.",
    "wrongAnswer": "on the chocolate wrapping paper."
  },
  {
    "id": "463",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Mystery of the Haunted House,\" Nelly will not turn into ______ to defeat the player.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Mystery of the Haunted House,\" Nelly will not turn into   Hel to defeat the player.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Mystery of the Haunted House,\" Nelly will not turn into Kotonoha to defeat the player.",
    "correctAnswer": "  Hel",
    "wrongAnswer": "Kotonoha"
  },
  {
    "id": "464",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Mystery of the Haunted House,\" the name of the small pumpkin at the entrance is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Mystery of the Haunted House,\" the name of the small pumpkin at the entrance is Bruce.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Mystery of the Haunted House,\" the name of the small pumpkin at the entrance is Endora.",
    "correctAnswer": "Bruce",
    "wrongAnswer": "Endora"
  },
  {
    "id": "465",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Winter Village,\" ______ is not needed to Repair the snow sledge.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Winter Village,\" Wooden Stick is not needed to Repair the snow sledge.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Winter Village,\" Inedible Red Fruit is not needed to Repair the snow sledge.",
    "correctAnswer": "Wooden Stick",
    "wrongAnswer": "Inedible Red Fruit"
  },
  {
    "id": "466",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Winter Village,\" ______ pulls the snow sledge.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Winter Village,\" Beebis pulls the snow sledge.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Winter Village,\" a Deer pulls the snow sledge.",
    "correctAnswer": "Beebis",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Deer"
  },
  {
    "id": "467",
    "questionTemplate": "Dragon Points can be used to trade for various items in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Dragon Points can be used to trade for various items in the Adventure Encyclopedia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Dragon Points can be used to trade for various items in the Monster Encyclopedia.",
    "correctAnswer": "the Adventure Encyclopedia",
    "wrongAnswer": "the Monster Encyclopedia"
  },
  {
    "id": "468",
    "questionTemplate": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating %s1",
    "correctQuestion": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating Dungeon Boss Monsters.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating Dungeon Normal Monsters.",
    "correctAnswer": "Dungeon Boss Monsters.",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dungeon Normal Monsters."
  },
  {
    "id": "469",
    "questionTemplate": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating %s1",
    "correctQuestion": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating Rare Elites.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating Normal Monsters.",
    "correctAnswer": "Rare Elites.",
    "wrongAnswer": "Normal Monsters."
  },
  {
    "id": "470",
    "questionTemplate": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating %s1",
    "correctQuestion": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating Eidolons",
    "wrongQuestion": "Dragon Points can be earned by defeating other players.",
    "correctAnswer": "Eidolons",
    "wrongAnswer": "other players."
  },
  {
    "id": "471",
    "questionTemplate": "Defeating the Dungeon Boss Monsters earns you ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Defeating the Dungeon Boss Monsters earns you Dragon Points.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Defeating the Dungeon Boss Monsters earns you Tokens.",
    "correctAnswer": "Dragon Points",
    "wrongAnswer": "Tokens"
  },
  {
    "id": "472",
    "questionTemplate": "When the character level reaches ______ you will receive an invitation from the Anglers Anonymous.",
    "correctQuestion": "When the character level reaches 40 you will receive an invitation from the Anglers Anonymous.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When the character level reaches 20 you will receive an invitation from the Anglers Anonymous.",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "wrongAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "id": "473",
    "questionTemplate": "The first Fishing Fisher that you met was ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The first Fishing Fisher that you met was Elle Fisher.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The first Fishing Fisher that you met was Fozzie Fisher.",
    "correctAnswer": "Elle Fisher",
    "wrongAnswer": "Fozzie Fisher"
  },
  {
    "id": "474",
    "questionTemplate": "The leader of the Penguin Bandits is not ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The leader of the Penguin Bandits is not Nymphet.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The leader of the Penguin Bandits is not Nebuchadnezzar.",
    "correctAnswer": "Nymphet",
    "wrongAnswer": "Nebuchadnezzar"
  },
  {
    "id": "475",
    "questionTemplate": "When the Fish King is caught, ______ suddenly appears to attack the fisherman.",
    "correctQuestion": "When the Fish King is caught, Nebuchadnezzar suddenly appears to attack the fisherman.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When the Fish King is caught, Nabopolassar suddenly appears to attack the fisherman.",
    "correctAnswer": "Nebuchadnezzar",
    "wrongAnswer": "Nabopolassar"
  },
  {
    "id": "476",
    "questionTemplate": "______ is the Anglers Anonymous CEO.",
    "correctQuestion": "Preston is the Anglers Anonymous CEO.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Myrna is the Anglers Anonymous CEO.",
    "correctAnswer": "Preston",
    "wrongAnswer": "Myrna"
  },
  {
    "id": "477",
    "questionTemplate": "The Demon Glutton in Alabastren Temple removes the seal from ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The Demon Glutton in Alabastren Temple removes the seal from the Thunder-Dragon King.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The Demon Glutton in Alabastren Temple removes the seal from the Sky Dragon King.",
    "correctAnswer": "the Thunder-Dragon King",
    "wrongAnswer": "the Sky Dragon King"
  },
  {
    "id": "478",
    "questionTemplate": "The legendary Thunder-Dragon King was sealed in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The legendary Thunder-Dragon King was sealed in Alabastren Temple.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The legendary Thunder-Dragon King was sealed in Demarech Mines.",
    "correctAnswer": "Alabastren Temple",
    "wrongAnswer": "Demarech Mines"
  },
  {
    "id": "479",
    "questionTemplate": "In Gydaie Glen, the Charm Queen removes the seal from ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Gydaie Glen, the Charm Queen removes the seal from the Sky Dragon King.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Gydaie Glen, the Charm Queen removes the seal from the Aqua-Dragon Queen.",
    "correctAnswer": "the Sky Dragon King",
    "wrongAnswer": "the Aqua-Dragon Queen"
  },
  {
    "id": "480",
    "questionTemplate": "The legendary Sky Dragon King was sealed in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The legendary Sky Dragon King was sealed in Gydaie Glen.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The legendary Sky Dragon King was sealed in Alabastren Temple.",
    "correctAnswer": "Gydaie Glen",
    "wrongAnswer": "Alabastren Temple"
  },
  {
    "id": "481",
    "questionTemplate": "In Demarech Mines, the Frozen Sorcerer removes the seal from ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, the Frozen Sorcerer removes the seal from the Aqua-Dragon Queen.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In Demarech Mines, the Frozen Sorcerer removes the seal from the Thunder-Dragon King.",
    "correctAnswer": "the Aqua-Dragon Queen",
    "wrongAnswer": "the Thunder-Dragon King"
  },
  {
    "id": "482",
    "questionTemplate": "The legendary Aqua-Dragon Queen was sealed in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The legendary Aqua-Dragon Queen was sealed in Demarech Mines.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The legendary Aqua-Dragon Queen was sealed in Gydaie Glen.",
    "correctAnswer": "Demarech Mines",
    "wrongAnswer": "Gydaie Glen"
  },
  {
    "id": "483",
    "questionTemplate": "Altogether there were ______ factions that participated in the battle for Vulture's Vale on the side of the allies.",
    "correctQuestion": "Altogether there were 6 factions that participated in the battle for Vulture's Vale on the side of the allies.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Altogether there were 4 factions that participated in the battle for Vulture's Vale on the side of the allies.",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "wrongAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "484",
    "questionTemplate": "In the ingredients for the potion making quest in Vulture's Vale, ______ is described as an alien organism.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the ingredients for the potion making quest in Vulture's Vale, Forest Land Crab is described as an alien organism.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the ingredients for the potion making quest in Vulture's Vale, Insect Remains is described as an alien organism.",
    "correctAnswer": "Forest Land Crab",
    "wrongAnswer": "Insect Remains"
  },
  {
    "id": "485",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Vulture's Vale, ______ fought alone at Black Tooth City.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Vulture's Vale, Tatiana fought alone at Black Tooth City.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Vulture's Vale, Shalen fought alone at Black Tooth City.",
    "correctAnswer": "Tatiana",
    "wrongAnswer": "Shalen"
  },
  {
    "id": "486",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Vulture's Vale, the Dark Legion used ______ to incur heavy losses among the Alliance.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Vulture's Vale, the Dark Legion used Scourge Artillery to incur heavy losses among the Alliance.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Vulture's Vale, the Dark Legion used Punishing Artillery to incur heavy losses among the Alliance.",
    "correctAnswer": "Scourge Artillery",
    "wrongAnswer": "Punishing Artillery"
  },
  {
    "id": "487",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, you are forced to jump from the Magic Circle in order to evade droves of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, you are forced to jump from the Magic Circle in order to evade droves of Wild Boar.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, you are forced to jump from the Magic Circle in order to evade droves of Runic Ghost.",
    "correctAnswer": "Wild Boar",
    "wrongAnswer": "Runic Ghost"
  },
  {
    "id": "489",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, the Sarpas strive to revive ______ at The Great Seal.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, the Sarpas strive to revive Giant Dragon at The Great Seal.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, the Sarpas strive to revive Demon at The Great Seal.",
    "correctAnswer": "Giant Dragon",
    "wrongAnswer": "Demon"
  },
  {
    "id": "490",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, ______ is responsible for passing on information for the Dark Legion.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, Icehoof Blitzer is responsible for passing on information for the Dark Legion.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, Demidrake is responsible for passing on information for the Dark Legion.",
    "correctAnswer": "Icehoof Blitzer",
    "wrongAnswer": "Demidrake"
  },
  {
    "id": "491",
    "questionTemplate": "On the front line of the battle, ______ opens Banoleth's Ancient Cage.",
    "correctQuestion": "On the front line of the battle, Horsemen of War opens Banoleth's Ancient Cage.",
    "wrongQuestion": "On the front line of the battle, a Fallen Angel opens Banoleth's Ancient Cage.",
    "correctAnswer": "Horsemen of War",
    "wrongAnswer": "a Fallen Angel"
  },
  {
    "id": "492",
    "questionTemplate": "The defences at the Carrion Barrier are strong, but ______ from Black Tooth City still manages to parachute onto the barrier.",
    "correctQuestion": "The defences at the Carrion Barrier are strong, but Forsaken Soldier from Black Tooth City still manages to parachute onto the barrier.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The defences at the Carrion Barrier are strong, but Blacktooth Werewolf from Black Tooth City still manages to parachute onto the barrier.",
    "correctAnswer": "Forsaken Soldier",
    "wrongAnswer": "Blacktooth Werewolf"
  },
  {
    "id": "493",
    "questionTemplate": "Chief Amon is the most formidable of warriors. ______ can make him afraid.",
    "correctQuestion": "Chief Amon is the most formidable of warriors. Deepsea Monstrosity can make him afraid.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Chief Amon is the most formidable of warriors. Tanner Jones can make him afraid.",
    "correctAnswer": "Deepsea Monstrosity",
    "wrongAnswer": "Tanner Jones"
  },
  {
    "id": "494",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, ______ is commander of the church army.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg,   Alex is commander of the church army.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, Anya is commander of the church army.",
    "correctAnswer": "  Alex",
    "wrongAnswer": "Anya"
  },
  {
    "id": "495",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, the Engineer Yakko who has an accident is a resident of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, the Engineer Yakko who has an accident is a resident of Meriland.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, the Engineer Yakko who has an accident is a resident of Feren Village.",
    "correctAnswer": "Meriland",
    "wrongAnswer": "Feren Village"
  },
  {
    "id": "496",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, Mac says that ______ must be protected.",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, Mac says that Selena must be protected.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, Mac says that Lawrence must be protected.",
    "correctAnswer": "Selena",
    "wrongAnswer": "Lawrence"
  },
  {
    "id": "497",
    "questionTemplate": "Vermilion thinks that everything that humans say ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Vermilion thinks that everything that humans say contradicts what they are thinking.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Vermilion thinks that everything that humans say is sincere.",
    "correctAnswer": "contradicts what they are thinking",
    "wrongAnswer": "is sincere"
  },
  {
    "id": "498",
    "questionTemplate": "The small bird beside Vermilion is her ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The small bird beside Vermilion is her master.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The small bird beside Vermilion is her pet.",
    "correctAnswer": "master",
    "wrongAnswer": "pet"
  },
  {
    "id": "499",
    "questionTemplate": "Vermilion's outfit was left to her by her ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Vermilion's outfit was left to her by her mother.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Vermilion's outfit was left to her by her master.",
    "correctAnswer": "mother",
    "wrongAnswer": "master"
  },
  {
    "id": "500",
    "questionTemplate": "Shirayuki thinks that ______ can also sometimes be a powerful weapon.",
    "correctQuestion": "Shirayuki thinks that tenderness can also sometimes be a powerful weapon.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Shirayuki thinks that tears can also sometimes be a powerful weapon.",
    "correctAnswer": "tenderness",
    "wrongAnswer": "tears"
  },
  {
    "id": "501",
    "questionTemplate": "Shirayuki's pet is a ______ called Momiji.",
    "correctQuestion": "Shirayuki's pet is a Pipe Fox called Momiji.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Shirayuki's pet is a Nekomata called Momiji.",
    "correctAnswer": "Pipe Fox",
    "wrongAnswer": "Nekomata"
  },
  {
    "id": "502",
    "questionTemplate": "Shirayuki is not proficient in the art of ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Shirayuki is not proficient in the art of Drama.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Shirayuki is not proficient in the art of Dance.",
    "correctAnswer": "Drama",
    "wrongAnswer": "Dance"
  },
  {
    "id": "503",
    "questionTemplate": "Kaiser Zeta's dream is ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Kaiser Zeta's dream is to fly toward to the sun.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Kaiser Zeta's dream is to conquer the world.",
    "correctAnswer": "to fly toward to the sun",
    "wrongAnswer": "to conquer the world"
  },
  {
    "id": "504",
    "questionTemplate": "Kaiser Zeta was created by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Kaiser Zeta was created by Daedalus.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Kaiser Zeta was created by Bahadur.",
    "correctAnswer": "Daedalus",
    "wrongAnswer": "Bahadur"
  },
  {
    "id": "505",
    "questionTemplate": "The power source fueling Kaiser Zeta stems from ______",
    "correctQuestion": "The power source fueling Kaiser Zeta stems from Cube of Gaia.",
    "wrongQuestion": "The power source fueling Kaiser Zeta stems from Cube of Magic.",
    "correctAnswer": "Cube of Gaia",
    "wrongAnswer": "Cube of Magic"
  },
  {
    "id": "506",
    "questionTemplate": "Hel believes that she has ______ brothers.",
    "correctQuestion": "Hel believes that she has 3 brothers.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Hel believes that she has 2 brothers.",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "507",
    "questionTemplate": "Hel's habits are similar to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Hel's habits are similar to Crow.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Hel's habits are similar to Owl.",
    "correctAnswer": "Crow",
    "wrongAnswer": "Owl"
  },
  {
    "id": "508",
    "questionTemplate": "Hel and ______ have a complicated past.",
    "correctQuestion": "Hel and Bealdor have a complicated past.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Hel and Alucard have a complicated past.",
    "correctAnswer": "Bealdor",
    "wrongAnswer": "Alucard"
  },
  {
    "id": "509",
    "questionTemplate": "Alucard thinks that strength is not only physical, but is also rooted in ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Alucard thinks that strength is not only physical, but is also rooted in heart and soul.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Alucard thinks that strength is not only physical, but is also rooted in memory.",
    "correctAnswer": "heart and soul",
    "wrongAnswer": "memory"
  },
  {
    "id": "510",
    "questionTemplate": "Alucard's unique dual blades can cut through ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Alucard's unique dual blades can cut through Time and Space.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Alucard's unique dual blades can cut through Chains and Soul Connections.",
    "correctAnswer": "Time and Space",
    "wrongAnswer": "Chains and Soul Connections"
  },
  {
    "id": "511",
    "questionTemplate": "Alucard has come to Terra in order to ______",
    "correctQuestion": "Alucard has come to Terra in order to make good on an old promise.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Alucard has come to Terra in order to to judge the world before the apocalypse.",
    "correctAnswer": "make good on an old promise",
    "wrongAnswer": "to judge the world before the apocalypse"
  },
  {
    "id": "2001",
    "questionTemplate": "Welcome to the Aura Kingdom Quiz! I am your host, Major Gerald.",
    "correctQuestion": "Welcome to the Aura Kingdom Quiz! I am your host, Major Gerald.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Welcome to the Aura Kingdom Quiz! I am your host, Major Gerald.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2002",
    "questionTemplate": "Allow me to explain the rules of this competition.",
    "correctQuestion": "Allow me to explain the rules of this competition.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Allow me to explain the rules of this competition.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2003",
    "questionTemplate": "I will give you 20 questions to answer.",
    "correctQuestion": "I will give you 20 questions to answer.",
    "wrongQuestion": "I will give you 20 questions to answer.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2004",
    "questionTemplate": "As you can see, there are two platforms, each labeled \"X\" or \"O\". To choose an answer, please stand on the corresponding platform.",
    "correctQuestion": "As you can see, there are two platforms, each labeled \"X\" or \"O\". To choose an answer, please stand on the corresponding platform.",
    "wrongQuestion": "As you can see, there are two platforms, each labeled \"X\" or \"O\". To choose an answer, please stand on the corresponding platform.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2005",
    "questionTemplate": "If you answer a question correctly, your score will increase. If you answer incorrectly, your score will decrease.",
    "correctQuestion": "If you answer a question correctly, your score will increase. If you answer incorrectly, your score will decrease.",
    "wrongQuestion": "If you answer a question correctly, your score will increase. If you answer incorrectly, your score will decrease.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2006",
    "questionTemplate": "But... and this is important... if you don't answer at all, your score will decrease EVEN MORE than for a wrong answer. So don't be shy!",
    "correctQuestion": "But... and this is important... if you don't answer at all, your score will decrease EVEN MORE than for a wrong answer. So don't be shy!",
    "wrongQuestion": "But... and this is important... if you don't answer at all, your score will decrease EVEN MORE than for a wrong answer. So don't be shy!",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2007",
    "questionTemplate": "When the quiz is over, we will send your reward to your mailbox.",
    "correctQuestion": "When the quiz is over, we will send your reward to your mailbox.",
    "wrongQuestion": "When the quiz is over, we will send your reward to your mailbox.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2008",
    "questionTemplate": "Unless, of course, your score is zero... then we can't send you anything.",
    "correctQuestion": "Unless, of course, your score is zero... then we can't send you anything.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Unless, of course, your score is zero... then we can't send you anything.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2009",
    "questionTemplate": "Are you ready? Got your thinking cap on? Then good luck!",
    "correctQuestion": "Are you ready? Got your thinking cap on? Then good luck!",
    "wrongQuestion": "Are you ready? Got your thinking cap on? Then good luck!",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2011",
    "questionTemplate": "Question %s1",
    "correctQuestion": "Question ",
    "wrongQuestion": "Question ",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2021",
    "questionTemplate": "Please choose a platform. The answer will be shown in 5 seconds.",
    "correctQuestion": "Please choose a platform. The answer will be shown in 5 seconds.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Please choose a platform. The answer will be shown in 5 seconds.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2022",
    "questionTemplate": "Correct! You scored ______ points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "correctQuestion": "Correct! You scored  points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Correct! You scored  points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2023",
    "questionTemplate": "Wrong! You lost ______ points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "correctQuestion": "Wrong! You lost  points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Wrong! You lost  points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2024",
    "questionTemplate": "No answer! You lost ______ points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "correctQuestion": "No answer! You lost  points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "wrongQuestion": "No answer! You lost  points. You will be teleported to the Ready Area in 3 seconds.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2025",
    "questionTemplate": "Alas, none of you has finished with 400 points. What a pity!",
    "correctQuestion": "Alas, none of you has finished with 400 points. What a pity!",
    "wrongQuestion": "Alas, none of you has finished with 400 points. What a pity!",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2031",
    "questionTemplate": "Thank you very much for participating!",
    "correctQuestion": "Thank you very much for participating!",
    "wrongQuestion": "Thank you very much for participating!",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2032",
    "questionTemplate": "Allow me to express my admiration for those of you who have finished with 400 points! Very impressive! You sure know your stuff!",
    "correctQuestion": "Allow me to express my admiration for those of you who have finished with 400 points! Very impressive! You sure know your stuff!",
    "wrongQuestion": "Allow me to express my admiration for those of you who have finished with 400 points! Very impressive! You sure know your stuff!",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2033",
    "questionTemplate": "Your reward will arrive in your mailbox shortly.",
    "correctQuestion": "Your reward will arrive in your mailbox shortly.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Your reward will arrive in your mailbox shortly.",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2034",
    "questionTemplate": "For those of you who didn't win a reward, don't despair! There's always next time. Study up on your Aura Kingdom trivia, and we'll see you then!",
    "correctQuestion": "For those of you who didn't win a reward, don't despair! There's always next time. Study up on your Aura Kingdom trivia, and we'll see you then!",
    "wrongQuestion": "For those of you who didn't win a reward, don't despair! There's always next time. Study up on your Aura Kingdom trivia, and we'll see you then!",
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "wrongAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "questionTemplate": "In the Fame Quest \"Rescue the Sprite\", the sprite was captured by ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Rescue the Sprite\", the sprite was captured by Radamog.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the Fame Quest \"Rescue the Sprite\", the sprite was captured by Indalam.",
    "correctAnswer": "Radamog",
    "wrongAnswer": "Indalam"
  },
  {
    "id": "488",
    "questionTemplate": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, a battle robot must be ridden to defeat ______",
    "correctQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, a battle robot must be ridden to defeat Giant Deadwood.",
    "wrongQuestion": "In the battle for Blizzard Berg, a battle robot must be ridden to defeat Giant Driftwood.",
    "correctAnswer": "Giant Deadwood",
    "wrongAnswer": "Giant Driftwood"
  },
  {
    "id": "138",
    "questionTemplate": "Temporal Golem Kelosa summons ______  becoming more resistant to damage.",
    "correctQuestion": "Temporal Golem Kelosa summons Void Crystals, becoming more resistant to damage.",
    "wrongQuestion": "Temporal Golem Kelosa summons  Temporal Crystals, becoming more resistant to damage.",
    "correctAnswer": "Void Crystals",
    "wrongAnswer": " Temporal Crystals"
  }
]
